<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_12270_38953872"> 
<user id ="MS_247167077"> 
	 <username>Groucho's Redbone Comrade (in Europe,brb)</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>24</age> 
	 <city>Lisbon</city> 
	 <province>Lisboa</province> 
	 <country>PT</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1204182900</date> 
 <body>^ Nope.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_12270_38954055"> 
<user id ="MS_45565737"> 
	 <username>Day Man: Fighter of the night man.</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>26</age> 
	 <city>Goodbye Beaumont (thanks for the whiskey)</city> 
	 <province>Texas</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1204183200</date> 
 <body>  I think it was Mitch Hedburg who said "I like the UPS guy, cause he's a drug dealer and he doesn't even know it."</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_12270_38954361"> 
<user id ="MS_45565737"> 
	 <username>Day Man: Fighter of the night man.</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>26</age> 
	 <city>Goodbye Beaumont (thanks for the whiskey)</city> 
	 <province>Texas</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1204183620</date> 
 <body>If I were the teacher, I would tell them I just created a MASSIVE project for them out of thin air. Anyone who tells me who took the money gets an automatic 100 and doesn't have to do it.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_12270_38954374"> 
<user id ="MS_11219867"> 
	 <username>President Puss</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>30</age> 
	 <city>Boonton Township</city> 
	 <province>New Jersey</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1204183680</date> 
 <body>Dood... WTF??!?!   This is another reason why, when I have kids, they will go to private schools.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_12270_38954796"> 
<user id ="MS_11219867"> 
	 <username>President Puss</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>30</age> 
	 <city>Boonton Township</city> 
	 <province>New Jersey</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1204184340</date> 
 <body>If my child deserves a black eye, a black eye my child should recieve.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_12270_38955098"> 
<user id ="MS_11219867"> 
	 <username>President Puss</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>30</age> 
	 <city>Boonton Township</city> 
	 <province>New Jersey</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1204184760</date> 
 <body>Not for every child, only for those who have worked hard for one.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_12270_38955676"> 
<user id ="MS_27502371"> 
	 <username>Erika</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>27</age> 
	 <city>Place everyone wants to be</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1204185600</date> 
 <body>  There are exceptions to the 4th Amendment in relation to public schools. Read this:  Public Schools .--In New Jersey v. T.L.O.,  108 the Court set forth the principles governing searches by public school authorities. The Fourth Amendment applies to searches conducted by public school officials because ''school officials act as representatives of the State, not merely as surrogates for the parents.''  109 However, ''the school setting requires some easing of the restrictions to which searches by public authorities are ordinarily subject.''  110 Neither the warrant requirement nor the probable cause standard is appropriate, the Court ruled. Instead, a simple reasonableness standard governs all searches of students' persons and effects by school authorities.  111 A search must be reasonable at its inception, i.e., there must be ''reasonable grounds for suspecting that the search will turn up evidence that the student has violated or is violating either the law or the rules of the school.''  112 School searches must also be reasonably related in scope to the circumstances justifying the interference, and ''not excessively intrusive in light of the age and sex of the student and the nature of the infraction.''  113 In applying these rules, the Court upheld as reasonable the search of a student's purse to determine whether the student, accused of violating a school rule by smoking in the lavatory, possessed cigarettes. The search for cigarettes uncovered evidence of drug activity held admissible in a prosecution under the juvenile laws.     Click here for source</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_12270_38956133"> 
<user id ="MS_90278368"> 
	 <username>Rob</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>29</age> 
	 <city>Colchester</city> 
	 <province>East</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1204186200</date> 
 <body>  Hey (completely off topic sorry, but I'll come back to it later) howcome the U.S. has the most restrictions on what we can send through the mail? They have more restrictions than Iran and Syria combined (even with their ban on almost anything of Israeli origin).  Now back to the topic, our teachers would just have kept us behind after school untill the envelope and $5 reappeared on the desk.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_12270_38957047"> 
<user id ="MS_247167077"> 
	 <username>Groucho's Redbone Comrade (in Europe,brb)</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>24</age> 
	 <city>Lisbon</city> 
	 <province>Lisboa</province> 
	 <country>PT</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1204187340</date> 
 <body>What if it didn't reappear for weeks?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_12270_38959010"> 
<user id ="MS_151213730"> 
	 <username>Mamma4</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>36</age> 
	 <city>Richland</city> 
	 <province>Washington</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1204190100</date> 
 <body>  Where does it state that a parent needs to be present?  As stated earlier, this is just a way to prepare our children for a police state.  I do not like it.  We are teaching our children that if someone asks to search them they need to ask for us.  We are their parents, We will be present for anything the school thinks they have a right to do.  And if they don't have a warrant then they better get one.  Just because my child is enrolled in school does not mean we as a family give up our rights.   I wonder if this is why people choose to home school?   From what I read in th OP, that an envelope disappeared.  Since they had no clue what happened to it they decided to search all of the children.  That is wrong.  And once again where were the parents.</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>