<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_30525_45768771"> 
<user id ="MS_358321294"> 
	 <username>Emergence</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>37</age> 
	 <city>Oregon</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215260400</date> 
 <body>The original "The Wicker Man"   THE 1973 ORIGINAL VERSION NOT the Remake.     I didn't see the remake but Im going to assume this was the ending:  Nicholas Cage jumps out of the wicker man at the last moment that its burning, performs Krag Maga on the village leader and several of the other pagans, disarming his gun taking it and grabbing the girl, Nick C. then gets into a car for a long car chase sequence with villagers in pursuit in their cars, with a hail of bullets following him, he crashes through a random fruit stand. Drives under a semi-truck, turning the car into a convertable, the cars following him crash into it. Then he slams into a firetruck which explodes. It seems like all is lost as the pagans surround a bruised and tattered and burned Nick Cage trapped in his car. Then the sound of helicopter blades:  Miraculously the ATF shows up in helicopters. ATF paratroupers leap out on rope ladders. The ATF burns the entire town to the ground like Waco. At the end of the movie a battlescarred Nickolas Cage, exhausted out of breath, gets praised by the leading ATF Commander (who is also Nick's dad) something like "Good job son, sorry I doubted you in Waco"   Then the credits roll, and some lame rap music plays with these lyrics: "Wicka, wicka, wicka; my n$gga, n$gga, n$gga"</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_30525_45768868"> 
<user id ="MS_67832205"> 
	 <username>THE DzA â˜®[happy]</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>20</age> 
	 <city>FRESNO</city> 
	 <province>CALIFORNIA</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215260520</date> 
 <body>Enemy at the gates</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_30525_45769556"> 
<user id ="MS_117412665"> 
	 <username>The Ninja formerly known as James</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>32</age> 
	 <city>BELLEVUE</city> 
	 <province>NEBRASKA</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215261600</date> 
 <body>  Only Monty Python would think of ending a movie with a musical number with a bunch of dudes on crosses. :)</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_30525_45769752"> 
<user id ="MS_147819654"> 
	 <username>Sir-Lionhart(Loves asian girl)</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>17</age> 
	 <city>MILWAUKEE</city> 
	 <province>Wisconsin</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215261840</date> 
 <body>When the guy got the girl at the end of that one movie.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_30525_45769850"> 
<user id ="MS_101859462"> 
	 <username>Alistair</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>18</age> 
	 <city>Congleton</city> 
	 <province>Northwest</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215262020</date> 
 <body>A few films with very memorable and some moving endings are:  The Shawshank Redemption Ghost ET Blade Runner Casablanca It's a wonderful life Citizen Kane</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_30525_45771704"> 
<user id ="MS_3420865"> 
	 <username>thatDUDEchris</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>24</age> 
	 <city>RANCHO CUCAMONGA</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215264840</date> 
 <body>fight club...buildings exploding to lose my mind, loved it  momento...left my jaw on the floor!  usual suspects....same side effect jaw still located on floor</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_30525_45772091"> 
<user id ="MS_317801027"> 
	 <username>!</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>99</age> 
	 <city>British Columbia</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>CA</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215265380</date> 
 <body> The only thing good about the ending to Citizen Kane is that it ended: boring. The credits are the highlight of the film.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_30525_45772256"> 
<user id ="MS_101859462"> 
	 <username>Alistair</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>18</age> 
	 <city>Congleton</city> 
	 <province>Northwest</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215265620</date> 
 <body>  Oh right, was that why it became the most acclaimed film of all time? Actually Citizen Kane is a brilliant film, it was highly influential, it was a landmark in filmmaking, it practically changed the way films are made, Orson Welles created a certain cinematography in the film that is revolutionary</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_30525_45773171"> 
<user id ="MS_30463441"> 
	 <username>Bobby Brakeout</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>17</age> 
	 <city>Portland</city> 
	 <province>Tennessee</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215266940</date> 
 <body>  Right here. Awesome ending.    Also, Se7en.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_30525_45773315"> 
<user id ="MS_317801027"> 
	 <username>!</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>99</age> 
	 <city>British Columbia</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>CA</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215267120</date> 
 <body> Little Known Fact: Orson Welles is in the Guiness Book Of World Records for eating more pork chops than any human being ever in one sitting. Look it up.</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>