<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_9463_46489286"> 
<user id ="MS_44198047"> 
	 <username>mê£äñìê</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>26</age> 
	 <city>Small Town</city> 
	 <province>Colorado</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216426260</date> 
 <body> If you think the oil companies are seeking a Republican President in the house this next election you are absolutely correct. If a Democrat happens to step in to the roll of President the price of fuel will increase. A Democratic President will raise taxes on fuel, making prices sky rocket.  You think prices are hitting you bank account hard now, just wait and see what will happen if a Democrat takes over as commander and chief. You think filling your car now is expensive, just watch and see.. You may be shocked at the outcome.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9463_46490869"> 
<user id ="MS_102902297"> 
	 <username>Jr.</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>28</age> 
	 <city>ILLINOIS</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216430940</date> 
 <body>Gas prices did go down. Or better said, the gas guzzlers went down south... of the border.   The US and Mexican press had a field day sensationalizing the events for several months, which in turn greatly affected tourism and Baja’s economy as over 40 percent of the Baja coastal region depends on tourism. Baja has experienced the economic pain that also punctuates for them the great binational economic interdependence.  Now it seems that despite the media fervor in reporting and sensationalizing Mexico’s problems with drug capos, Americans are flocking back to Baja. Why?  Saving money, trumps fear. Gasoline prices now over $4.50 a gallon in San Diego is available anywhere in Baja for around $2.55 a gallon. And the stampede of US trucks buying diesel fuel at $2.20 a gallon versus over $5 a gallon in San Diego, has caught Baja shorthanded an unable to keep up with the demand. Once again the economic interdependence is evident.  Robert Kline from Orange County waiting to fuel up his Ford pickup said that once he began reading and seen on nightly news about all the cars crossing for gas, he figured things can’t be that bad, so he decided to come back to Baja that was his favorite weekend retreat. Like Kline, others are beginning to see that things are OK, and they too will begin to travel to Baja. So things will go back to normal during the summer months.  http://hispanicvista.com/HVC/Columnist/posiojr/070608Patrick_Osi o.htm  BTW Mexico's gas prices go up only by inflation rate, where here in the US they are set by the individual sellers (companies).</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9463_46499493"> 
<user id ="MS_8225318"> 
	 <username>dujac</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>49</age> 
	 <city>Hot Springs</city> 
	 <province>Arkansas</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216454040</date> 
 <body>  it's called the 'law of supply and demand'  something that few seem to acknowledge</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9463_46504214"> 
<user id ="MS_385379064"> 
	 <username>El King of this Silly Avatar</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>33</age> 
	 <city>Garfield Hts.</city> 
	 <province>Ohio</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216462380</date> 
 <body>   Try your left foot.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9463_46505476"> 
<user id ="MS_374581065"> 
	 <username>Black~Jack is so gay - but likes girls too</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>17</age> 
	 <city>Aitkin</city> 
	 <province>Minnesota</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216464480</date> 
 <body>yeah it is a fluctuation but the fluctuations will probably result in the gas going down... I am not kidding you, they might be drilling right now and we need people to drill.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9463_46505511"> 
<user id ="MS_374581065"> 
	 <username>Black~Jack is so gay - but likes girls too</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>17</age> 
	 <city>Aitkin</city> 
	 <province>Minnesota</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216464540</date> 
 <body>  whoa that is expensive</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9463_46505563"> 
<user id ="MS_374581065"> 
	 <username>Black~Jack is so gay - but likes girls too</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>17</age> 
	 <city>Aitkin</city> 
	 <province>Minnesota</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216464600</date> 
 <body>  yeah the had pretty much topped off in my own opinion... I don't see it going any higher so that is good news.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9463_46515854"> 
<user id ="MS_335313387"> 
	 <username>Ryan</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>23</age> 
	 <city>EUGENE</city> 
	 <province>Oregon</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216481400</date> 
 <body>  Again, the knowledge you impart on us peons goes far too unappreciated.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9463_46520943"> 
<user id ="MS_8225318"> 
	 <username>dujac</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>49</age> 
	 <city>Hot Springs</city> 
	 <province>Arkansas</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216489020</date> 
 <body>  you're a peon?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9463_46521056"> 
<user id ="MS_335313387"> 
	 <username>Ryan</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>23</age> 
	 <city>EUGENE</city> 
	 <province>Oregon</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216489200</date> 
 <body> Relatively speaking.</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>