<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_29389_46998397"> 
<user id ="MS_393218373"> 
	 <username>Astro-Creep</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>18</age> 
	 <city>NEW YORK,</city> 
	 <province>New York</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217268120</date> 
 <body>One of the best shocker film IMO  This film is disturbingly spectacular and one of the best revenge film ever.  Kill Bill eat your heart out :)   Was it the uncut version why they shove the broken bottle in her erm erm you know what during the rape scene? Ouch that scene was gruesome....This film is technically a lesson to men...  Lesson being Don't fuck with a woman otherwise, she'll cut your balls off in the bath :)</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_46998656"> 
<user id ="MS_3420865"> 
	 <username>thatDUDEchris</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>24</age> 
	 <city>RANCHO CUCAMONGA</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217268420</date> 
 <body>never seen it but im renting it tommorrow becuase of this thread thank u :)</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_46998724"> 
<user id ="MS_3420865"> 
	 <username>thatDUDEchris</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>24</age> 
	 <city>RANCHO CUCAMONGA</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217268480</date> 
 <body>most grusome rape scene thougth irreversible, but i need to see this joint to compare really so it might be a premature opinion...but these types of shock films are good fun</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_46999832"> 
<user id ="MS_393218373"> 
	 <username>Astro-Creep</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>18</age> 
	 <city>NEW YORK,</city> 
	 <province>New York</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217269620</date> 
 <body>  The film is brilliant, i watch it on horror channel, i'm still waiting to get it and find it cheap on DVD, 15 pound is way too much. But trust me this film will make you look at women in a different light lol.   Another few great recommendations for horror from the 1980s  The Burning Silent Night, Deadly Night  I'm Downloading them currently</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47000019"> 
<user id ="MS_3420865"> 
	 <username>thatDUDEchris</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>24</age> 
	 <city>RANCHO CUCAMONGA</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217269860</date> 
 <body>nice i have a dvd planet by my house and they have a bunch of these old cult type horror joints im see if i can find it there...cuz im not sure my video store will have this one...</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47001329"> 
<user id ="MS_393218373"> 
	 <username>Astro-Creep</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>18</age> 
	 <city>NEW YORK,</city> 
	 <province>New York</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217271120</date> 
 <body>Meh  Netflix will definately have them   Or just download Utorrent and find the films via torrent and watch them on the good old compy or put them on DVD :)   That's what i'm gonna do with the one i'm Downloading, because i cant find them over here and plus side one of them ain't even on DVD release, which is Silent Night Deadly Night 3.  Juss download and burn to dvd :)</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47002215"> 
<user id ="MS_64197263"> 
	 <username>FightAgainstFascism</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>25</age> 
	 <city>LAS VEGAS</city> 
	 <province>Nevada</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217272260</date> 
 <body>They showed this in drive-ins? Damn america sure has changed in 20 years.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47002440"> 
<user id ="MS_158512037"> 
	 <username>ζΩΜβΙε</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>34</age> 
	 <city>βμττ§εχ³</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>YE</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217272500</date> 
 <body>I was 11 or 12 when I first and last saw this.  I think it was the first full frontal I'd ever seen. I vaguely remember gettin a chubby.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47002619"> 
<user id ="MS_2278378"> 
	 <username>Surf</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>27</age> 
	 <city>Riverside (No Longer San Diego :(</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217272740</date> 
 <body>  I suppose that would be true if you're a rapist. Us norms already know women are nuts.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47002634"> 
<user id ="MS_3420865"> 
	 <username>thatDUDEchris</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>24</age> 
	 <city>RANCHO CUCAMONGA</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217272740</date> 
 <body>a chubby hahhahahah</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>