<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_10707_51810701"> 
<user id ="MS_33312659"> 
	 <username>~@~ಌ~ß~є~®~</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>27</age> 
	 <city>ORLANDO</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225190640</date> 
 <body>She's constantly being told what to, what to say, etc. Rightly, so. She's a complete retard! Didn't MCain know what he was getting himself into when choosing this chick?? When she speaks for herself...horrible things happen for the GOP candidate. They should have known better!   CNN) -- Some aides to Sen. John McCain say they weren't happy that running mate Sarah Palin went off script Sunday and turned attention back to the controversy over her wardrobe.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10707_51810923"> 
<user id ="MS_33312659"> 
	 <username>~@~ಌ~ß~є~®~</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>27</age> 
	 <city>ORLANDO</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225190880</date> 
 <body>Several McCain advisers suggested that they have become increasingly frustrated with what one aide described as Palin "going rogue."</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10707_51811057"> 
<user id ="MS_58567723"> 
	 <username>Charlie Bravo</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>36</age> 
	 <city>AUSTIN</city> 
	 <province>TEXAS</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225191060</date> 
 <body>She's a maverick.   *wink*</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10707_51811455"> 
<user id ="MS_55806833"> 
	 <username>Little Orphan Angie</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>30</age> 
	 <city>Surrounded by sociopaths in</city> 
	 <province>Missouri</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225191480</date> 
 <body>I love this line in the article:  "A Palin aide, however, told CNN that the governor clearly felt like she had to say something to defend herself, because "that's really not who she is."    What's that old saying? If it walks like a duck.....   I don't care that the RNC paid for the wardrobe and it was not illegal. I find it excessive and wasteful. Furthermore; her attempt(s) to justify it are lame.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10707_51811610"> 
<user id ="MS_93458445"> 
	 <username>Indy11</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>84</age> 
	 <city>The Bitten Apple</city> 
	 <province>New York</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225191720</date> 
 <body>It is possible that Palin's strengths as a personality were not capitalized properly by the McCain campaign. Her expensive makeover, for example, might not have been so radically necessary if the idea were to push the hockey mom image more.  But I think there are some pretty obvious reasons why the campaign wants to control Palin rather tightly. Upon introduction of Palin, the talk was as if Obama and Palin were the ones directly contesting for office.  This obviously would be damaging to McCain so you would have to think that McCain's advisers would want to redirect the focus on the main candidate and, also, bring Palin under wing in terms of talking points ... the way that the McCain advisers see the issues to be.  Rollins refers to the problem as mishandling Palin which does not underscore whether he saw Palin as an asset for substantive issues.  Bill Kristol, an early and still vocal champion of Palin feels that she should have been let loose to just speak her mind ... within bounds, presumably.  Either way, her role was to keep the hopes of a major BOP base alive and active and she has done that.  That there are GOP opinion leaders that have moved away from the campaign to support Obama isn't simply a matter of Palin having been mishandled, imo.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10707_51812163"> 
<user id ="MS_58567723"> 
	 <username>Charlie Bravo</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>36</age> 
	 <city>AUSTIN</city> 
	 <province>TEXAS</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225192380</date> 
 <body>  Personally, I rather think that, like it or not, if one is voting for McCain for POTUS, one is also, essentially, voting for Palin for the same office, at some point. 72 is a seasoned age, and it could be argued that the John McCain of 72 is far from the John McCain of 64. At any rate, the chances of Palin stepping into the position some time in the next 4 years is significant.  That having been said, this is the woman who flatly stated that the VPOTUS runs the Senate, and can really get in there and mix it up and change things with the senators.  *shudder*</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10707_51812409"> 
<user id ="MS_232205627"> 
	 <username>The Merciless Package</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>18</age> 
	 <city>VA BCH</city> 
	 <province>Virginia</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225192680</date> 
 <body>Like I said before. Get a time machine and bring McCain 00 back from the past to beat the snot out of McCain 08.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10707_51812450"> 
<user id ="MS_58567723"> 
	 <username>Charlie Bravo</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>36</age> 
	 <city>AUSTIN</city> 
	 <province>TEXAS</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225192740</date> 
 <body>  QFT.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10707_51812458"> 
<user id ="MS_93458445"> 
	 <username>Indy11</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>84</age> 
	 <city>The Bitten Apple</city> 
	 <province>New York</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225192740</date> 
 <body>   Oh, from the outside looking in, you're right.  But from inside the McCain campaign ... the notion that a candidate runs with a verity that he may die due to his age and health in office isn't in the playbook. So it is McCain first, Palin second and only in a supporting role.  Palin stealing headlines from Obama is one thing but also pushing McCain off the headlines is not acceptable.  It was important to get the base back with him because his position with them hasn't always been a totally warm and fuzzy experience. Palin was the answer, it seems. The question really is, though, how big is that base today compared to previous elections?  Vocal, the base may be but how many are still in that base? I have my doubts that it is as big as it once was. It is still sizable and McCain needs them to have a prayer of chance of winning but I am a little skeptical about its current size partly because of Palin and what her stronpoints at re-activating that base happen to be.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10707_51812646"> 
<user id ="MS_58567723"> 
	 <username>Charlie Bravo</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>36</age> 
	 <city>AUSTIN</city> 
	 <province>TEXAS</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225192980</date> 
 <body>  Good point, as always, old friend.</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>