<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_8834_36690401"> 
<user id ="MS_175576456"> 
	 <username>[Queen] Laila.™</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>17</age> 
	 <city>Great city of</city> 
	 <province>London and South East</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1200611760</date> 
 <body>  Lol, Oyster card :)  ..  Like so. Has your picture and name and as Im 17 and in education, I get free transport.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_36690421"> 
<user id ="MS_175576456"> 
	 <username>[Queen] Laila.™</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>17</age> 
	 <city>Great city of</city> 
	 <province>London and South East</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1200611760</date> 
 <body>..</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_36690425"> 
<user id ="MS_175576456"> 
	 <username>[Queen] Laila.™</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>17</age> 
	 <city>Great city of</city> 
	 <province>London and South East</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1200611820</date> 
 <body>Ah picture's not coming up :(</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_37117330"> 
<user id ="MS_41813372"> 
	 <username>winston smith</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>108</age> 
	 <city>e-London</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1201280040</date> 
 <body>http://groups.yahoo.com/group/osint/message/105233   why do you think that ken is the man to stay in london,  i dont care about how he compares to other candidates,  i want to know what specifically you think is good about him</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_37118425"> 
<user id ="MS_41813372"> 
	 <username>winston smith</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>108</age> 
	 <city>e-London</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1201281180</date> 
 <body>     you cant credit ken for the london olympics, east london is as prime a location for an olympics, all that waste land in east london needed something doing with it, ken was in the right place at the right time and jumped on the bandwagon,  seb coe ran the bid to the olympic commitee, big business sponsored it, david beckham swung the vote  ANY mayor would have said yes to the olympics considering the prestige atatched to it,   personally i think the olympics will be a big waste of money that wont actually help the people who live in east london much, just price them out of their own areas  i also disagree with you on the transport for london, yes the tories ballsed up on things a while ago, but a lot of time has passed since then, a lot of money has been spent on the underground since ken got in power and the only difference in service has been the price of ticket as far as i can see and i use it every day,  there was the fiasco of bob kielly or whatever he's called, the dude who ran new yorks subway, he did an interview with the evening standard where he confessed he was an alcoholic and a waste of our money, but ken stuck with him, that guy is on a whopping big contract, between 1-400k a year, i dont remember exactly, google it, but he got paid like a prince to get fucking pissed everyday    what kids get free transport? i never had free transport EVER when i was growing up, screw these free transport kids, they need to learn the value of money at some point otherwise your just breeding the next welfare generation</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_37139349"> 
<user id ="MS_175576456"> 
	 <username>[Queen] Laila.™</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>17</age> 
	 <city>Great city of</city> 
	 <province>London and South East</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1201318320</date> 
 <body>"what kids get free transport? i never had free transport EVER when i was growing up, screw these free transport kids, they need to learn the value of money at some point otherwise your just breeding the next welfare generation"  Hey! I like my free transport tyvm!  And besides, I know value of money.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_37140750"> 
<user id ="MS_41813372"> 
	 <username>winston smith</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>108</age> 
	 <city>e-London</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1201323480</date> 
 <body>maybe true,   but if you had to pay 30 quid a week out of your own wages to get transport that was usually either late, overcrowded, disrupted or dangerous, you would be a lot more concerned with who runs it and how much they charge  if i got something for free, i would be satisfied with any standard of service as it hasnt cost me anything  by giving you free transport ken is effectively trying to buy off the next generation of voters who are more likely to vote than someone with a fulltime job and family and commitments, and giving the bill to the rest of us,  for every free student transport pass, that is 1500 quid a year roughly he is adding onto the rest of londons travel costs  you will spend more of your life paying full price than on childrens free pass, will u still be as grateful when your 30yrs old and having to pay up to 40 or 50 a week on travel costs because more and more potential voters get free travel passes and you have to pay the bill?   there is no real need for teenagers to have free transport, non   old people, disabled people yes   young people no,  i agree with discounted travel for the young, but free..... thats taking the piss and shameless aimed at getting new voters    </body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_37197384"> 
<user id ="MS_130303483"> 
	 <username>Andy</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>35</age> 
	 <city>UK</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country></country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1201424940</date> 
 <body>whoever taps spoons on their knees whilst singing chaz and dave songs, and offers free jellied eels will get elected.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_37197971"> 
<user id ="MS_130303483"> 
	 <username>Andy</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>35</age> 
	 <city>UK</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country></country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1201425780</date> 
 <body>In my area of East Yorkshire, I don't think we have a BNP candidate.  I would vote for them in the next election though, as a protest against all the scum they are letting into the country.  Britain is full.  No more please.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_37199016"> 
<user id ="MS_130303483"> 
	 <username>Andy</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>35</age> 
	 <city>UK</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country></country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1201427220</date> 
 <body>I am not racist, but I don't want any more people in Britain, whatever colour they are.  60 million should now be capped. </body> 
 </post> 
</posts>