<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_8834_36609116"> 
<user id ="MS_41813372"> 
	 <username>winston smith</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>108</age> 
	 <city>e-London</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1200494640</date> 
 <body>ive not heard that boris will scrap free transport,   is that free transport for who? old people, i dont think he would be allowed to do that, people would screw</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_36609641"> 
<user id ="MS_41813372"> 
	 <username>winston smith</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>108</age> 
	 <city>e-London</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1200495180</date> 
 <body>infact who apart from old and disabled people get free transport?  i never had free transport ever,   infact this last week has cost me about 140 quid because of a broken oyster machine and its knock on effects  theres me sluggin my guts out and ppl get free transport?   im gettin sick of TFL, they treat you like cattle and mug you off when something goes wrong and it never ends    infact that settles it, im not voting for ken purely because of TFL, they disgust me as a company, and the worst thing is I am dependant on them.... I give them money everyday</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_36610158"> 
<user id ="MS_41813372"> 
	 <username>winston smith</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>108</age> 
	 <city>e-London</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1200495720</date> 
 <body>    lol  the first point is quite an outlandish claim to make, boris has only mentioned london in the house of commons once, are you sure?????   i agree the fact he is from london and always lived here is a good point, but it doesnt mean he hasnt been filling his boots at our expense in the meantime like the rest of them, ken brought in bob from new york to sort out the tube, the guy was a raging alcoholic who had a breakdown, did an interview in the standard saying he hasnt done anything and is still gettin paid   </body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_36661229"> 
<user id ="MS_175576456"> 
	 <username>[Queen] Laila.™</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>17</age> 
	 <city>Great city of</city> 
	 <province>London and South East</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1200574140</date> 
 <body>  Ouch, poor you.  I dunno about you but I get free transport. I love me oyster card tho It is a bitch replacing it if it gets lost.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_36664066"> 
<user id ="MS_90278368"> 
	 <username>Rob</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>29</age> 
	 <city>Colchester</city> 
	 <province>East</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1200577200</date> 
 <body>  Oyster card? Bare in mind I'm out in the sticks and we're behind the times.........  We've only just replaced the horse and cart with one of these new fangled bus contraptions......</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_36690401"> 
<user id ="MS_175576456"> 
	 <username>[Queen] Laila.™</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>17</age> 
	 <city>Great city of</city> 
	 <province>London and South East</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1200611760</date> 
 <body>  Lol, Oyster card :)  ..  Like so. Has your picture and name and as Im 17 and in education, I get free transport.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_36690421"> 
<user id ="MS_175576456"> 
	 <username>[Queen] Laila.™</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>17</age> 
	 <city>Great city of</city> 
	 <province>London and South East</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1200611760</date> 
 <body>..</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_36690425"> 
<user id ="MS_175576456"> 
	 <username>[Queen] Laila.™</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>17</age> 
	 <city>Great city of</city> 
	 <province>London and South East</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1200611820</date> 
 <body>Ah picture's not coming up :(</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_37117330"> 
<user id ="MS_41813372"> 
	 <username>winston smith</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>108</age> 
	 <city>e-London</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1201280040</date> 
 <body>http://groups.yahoo.com/group/osint/message/105233   why do you think that ken is the man to stay in london,  i dont care about how he compares to other candidates,  i want to know what specifically you think is good about him</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_37118425"> 
<user id ="MS_41813372"> 
	 <username>winston smith</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>108</age> 
	 <city>e-London</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1201281180</date> 
 <body>     you cant credit ken for the london olympics, east london is as prime a location for an olympics, all that waste land in east london needed something doing with it, ken was in the right place at the right time and jumped on the bandwagon,  seb coe ran the bid to the olympic commitee, big business sponsored it, david beckham swung the vote  ANY mayor would have said yes to the olympics considering the prestige atatched to it,   personally i think the olympics will be a big waste of money that wont actually help the people who live in east london much, just price them out of their own areas  i also disagree with you on the transport for london, yes the tories ballsed up on things a while ago, but a lot of time has passed since then, a lot of money has been spent on the underground since ken got in power and the only difference in service has been the price of ticket as far as i can see and i use it every day,  there was the fiasco of bob kielly or whatever he's called, the dude who ran new yorks subway, he did an interview with the evening standard where he confessed he was an alcoholic and a waste of our money, but ken stuck with him, that guy is on a whopping big contract, between 1-400k a year, i dont remember exactly, google it, but he got paid like a prince to get fucking pissed everyday    what kids get free transport? i never had free transport EVER when i was growing up, screw these free transport kids, they need to learn the value of money at some point otherwise your just breeding the next welfare generation</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>