<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_8834_37211270"> 
<user id ="MS_137780733"> 
	 <username>Nikokvaj</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>38</age> 
	 <city>Hovedstaden</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>DK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1201441980</date> 
 <body>  is it called danish barbecue or feuer und wasser?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_37229329"> 
<user id ="MS_137780733"> 
	 <username>Nikokvaj</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>38</age> 
	 <city>Hovedstaden</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>DK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1201463820</date> 
 <body>I did watch it, all they did was burn the Koran, no biggie</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_37244266"> 
<user id ="MS_137780733"> 
	 <username>Nikokvaj</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>38</age> 
	 <city>Hovedstaden</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>DK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1201499280</date> 
 <body>  That's probably why it didn't move me, I'm used to that stuff, it's all over the political debates</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_37244304"> 
<user id ="MS_41813372"> 
	 <username>winston smith</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>108</age> 
	 <city>e-London</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1201499400</date> 
 <body>i dont have any questions about livingstone,  i know enough about him to not vote for him  those videos are pretty useless  i would be more interested if you could provide me with any links to boris johnson             im really puzzled as to why you support him so blindly? i would be more interested in knowing your reasons</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_37244823"> 
<user id ="MS_137780733"> 
	 <username>Nikokvaj</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>38</age> 
	 <city>Hovedstaden</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>DK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1201500600</date> 
 <body>Are you writing yourself?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_37244828"> 
<user id ="MS_294564738"> 
	 <username>Fascist</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>28</age> 
	 <city>CA</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country></country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1201500600</date> 
 <body>    No one gives a shit about London. That city is the bloody UN. So many different peoples it is a shithole.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_37245207"> 
<user id ="MS_294564738"> 
	 <username>Fascist</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>28</age> 
	 <city>CA</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country></country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1201501500</date> 
 <body>    Yet, you did just replied. Dumbass, aren't you? I may be a little harsh, but I am no troll.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_37251640"> 
<user id ="MS_41813372"> 
	 <username>winston smith</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>108</age> 
	 <city>e-London</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1201511340</date> 
 <body>    dude id vote for boris if it definatally meant getting rid of ken,  my one beef with london is transport for london which ken is the boss of, im guessing as a lorry driver you dont have as much experience of the underground and buses in london as others,  London underground is a fucking joke, everyday is a chore because of the tube, i hate TFL more than i hate waking up, and im not a morning person   also i think ken is fiddling the books, an alcoholic and he is using schemes like free transport for kids who are approaching voting age to get votes,   that scheme has just popped up out of nowhere around election time and watch it will disappear too,  im pretty sure that 'in the spirit of promoting democracy' the mayors office will organise trips to the ballots for all these free transport kids   .......... IN THE MEANTIME CUNTS LIKE ME HAVE TO PICK UP THE BILL AND GET CHARGED EXTRA WHEN THE OYSTER MACHINE LETS US THROUGH BUT DOESNT SCAN OUR CARD PROPERLY  IF YOU WANT TO COMPLAIN YOU NEED TO GET IN TOUCH WITH SOME COMPANY OUT OF LONDON WHO DONT EVEN REPLY TO YOU   thats kens London     i would like to re-clariffy i do not support boris, i prob wont vote for him,    i would like you to show me some proof that he is a racist   its quite funny you say that as it was mayor livingstone who got suspended and had to get an appeal whitewash after comparing a JEWISH JOURNALIST TO A NAZI CONCENTRATION CAMP GUARD    Plus, socialism is a con, it makes the working man think it is looking out for him, but just keeps him happy at the bottom of the ladder, rather than give him the oppotunity to get more from life</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_37251758"> 
<user id ="MS_41813372"> 
	 <username>winston smith</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>108</age> 
	 <city>e-London</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1201511520</date> 
 <body>     says the spoof profile from canada where its all going down right    mug   </body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_37259926"> 
<user id ="MS_41813372"> 
	 <username>winston smith</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>108</age> 
	 <city>e-London</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1201520400</date> 
 <body>ive explained to you a few times already i wont be voting for boris   i dont really like any of the candidates,       i think your pulling my leg anyway mate   youve not given me a good enough reason for voting for him so i'll have to assume your gettin paid to promote him  </body> 
 </post> 
</posts>