<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_8834_36604675"> 
<user id ="MS_175576456"> 
	 <username>[Queen] Laila.™</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>17</age> 
	 <city>Great city of</city> 
	 <province>London and South East</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1200489420</date> 
 <body>Meh, I hit my B Day before the elections but I know the majority in mine don't care for politics, pity but I don't think I could change their mind :)  Then again .. I could threaten our free transport may be changed under the other two :D</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_36607289"> 
<user id ="MS_175576456"> 
	 <username>[Queen] Laila.™</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>17</age> 
	 <city>Great city of</city> 
	 <province>London and South East</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1200492720</date> 
 <body>Im only a Labour supporter when its a choice between Tory and Labour. Then again, who does like tories, I haven't met 1 teen that likes conservative yet.  And yeah, I may just do that.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_36608684"> 
<user id ="MS_41813372"> 
	 <username>winston smith</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>108</age> 
	 <city>e-London</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1200494220</date> 
 <body>hmm,   i can appreciate what your both saying esp if you have benefitted from his decisions   i think london is better now than it was before him, lookin back london was a grimey place not long ago, it still has its problems but there are a lot more good points than there a few years ago  but this is what i think about ken, he is essentially a gambler, a lot of the projects he has launched are with borrowed money, that means that the project needs to pay for itself or WE get the bill, you wont get this bill through the mail, everything else will slowly get more expensive,   my personal opinion is that ken hasnt opened THAT many doors for londoners, just a few more for the those who can afford it,  ive worked in a lot of places with a whole range of people and ive worked with some reprobates, people so thick its painful to look at them at times  i can only assume that its not that hard to find work, it just depends on how badly u want the work or what your pride will allow you to do,  i wouldnt vote for him just cos i worked for him directly or indirectly, job is a job is a job, u could just as easily get work for a construction or media company with a conservative on the board of directors   my point is tho, i dont know if kens gambles will pay off, i hope so, but ultimately it is out of our hands and time will tell,  if tony blair and his lot are anything to go by, we could be in trouble   boris is funny at times, and i think his bufoonery is exagerated as he is reported to have a good business record, but i dont trust the tories,    going on personalities i think ken has had his turn, a lot of blind eyes have been turned and he will get caught soon doing something that could effect our reputation,  boris is a mug ken is a c*nt the liberal dude is a gay copper  turd sandwich or giant douche anyone?     if he runs i might vote greg dyke who has a fantastic surname, good record, stood up to the gov when he needed to and suffered as a consequence but it showed he has some balls, he is from london, lives in london and isnt affliated to any of the partys</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_36609116"> 
<user id ="MS_41813372"> 
	 <username>winston smith</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>108</age> 
	 <city>e-London</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1200494640</date> 
 <body>ive not heard that boris will scrap free transport,   is that free transport for who? old people, i dont think he would be allowed to do that, people would screw</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_36609641"> 
<user id ="MS_41813372"> 
	 <username>winston smith</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>108</age> 
	 <city>e-London</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1200495180</date> 
 <body>infact who apart from old and disabled people get free transport?  i never had free transport ever,   infact this last week has cost me about 140 quid because of a broken oyster machine and its knock on effects  theres me sluggin my guts out and ppl get free transport?   im gettin sick of TFL, they treat you like cattle and mug you off when something goes wrong and it never ends    infact that settles it, im not voting for ken purely because of TFL, they disgust me as a company, and the worst thing is I am dependant on them.... I give them money everyday</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_36610158"> 
<user id ="MS_41813372"> 
	 <username>winston smith</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>108</age> 
	 <city>e-London</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1200495720</date> 
 <body>    lol  the first point is quite an outlandish claim to make, boris has only mentioned london in the house of commons once, are you sure?????   i agree the fact he is from london and always lived here is a good point, but it doesnt mean he hasnt been filling his boots at our expense in the meantime like the rest of them, ken brought in bob from new york to sort out the tube, the guy was a raging alcoholic who had a breakdown, did an interview in the standard saying he hasnt done anything and is still gettin paid   </body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_36661229"> 
<user id ="MS_175576456"> 
	 <username>[Queen] Laila.™</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>17</age> 
	 <city>Great city of</city> 
	 <province>London and South East</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1200574140</date> 
 <body>  Ouch, poor you.  I dunno about you but I get free transport. I love me oyster card tho It is a bitch replacing it if it gets lost.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_36664066"> 
<user id ="MS_90278368"> 
	 <username>Rob</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>29</age> 
	 <city>Colchester</city> 
	 <province>East</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1200577200</date> 
 <body>  Oyster card? Bare in mind I'm out in the sticks and we're behind the times.........  We've only just replaced the horse and cart with one of these new fangled bus contraptions......</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_36690401"> 
<user id ="MS_175576456"> 
	 <username>[Queen] Laila.™</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>17</age> 
	 <city>Great city of</city> 
	 <province>London and South East</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1200611760</date> 
 <body>  Lol, Oyster card :)  ..  Like so. Has your picture and name and as Im 17 and in education, I get free transport.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8834_36690421"> 
<user id ="MS_175576456"> 
	 <username>[Queen] Laila.™</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>17</age> 
	 <city>Great city of</city> 
	 <province>London and South East</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1200611760</date> 
 <body>..</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>