<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
 <post id="MS_10340_40251050">
      <user id="MS_110882268">
        <username>mrgone</username>
        <sex>M</sex>
        <age>52</age>
        <city>TUCKER</city>
        <province>Georgia</province>
        <country>US</country>
      </user>
      <date>1206279420</date>
      <body>Well Henry Ford powered his first model T with hemp seed oil. Maybe our fucked up gov't could change the law about growing hemp.</body>
    </post> 
 <post id="MS_10340_40257353">
      <user id="MS_321984954">
        <username>Pallas Athene</username>
        <sex>F</sex>
        <age>49</age>
        <city>North Carolina</city>
        <province/>
        <country>US</country>
      </user>
      <date>1206287340</date>
      <body>  Didn't know much about hemp, so I looked it up. Seems like we should allow it here!  Hemp (from Old English hænep, see cannabis (etymology)) is the common name for plants of the entire family of Cannabis, although the term is often used to refer only to Cannabis strains cultivated for industrial (non-drug) use. Hemp is cultivated virtually everywhere in the world except for the United States, and its cultivation in western countries is growing steadily. For example, Canadian Hempseed exports surged 300% last year[citation needed]. China, and other eastern countries, never prohibited its cultivation and use it extensively.  Industrial hemp has thousands of potential uses, from paper to textiles to biodegradable plastics to health food to fuel but it has not been the great commercial success that the enthusiast hoped for in countries where it is legal to harvest. It is one of the fastest growing biomasses on the planet, and one of the earliest domesticated plants known. It also runs parallel with the "Green Future" objectives that are becoming increasingly popular. Hemp requires little to no pesticides, replenishes soil with nutrients and nitrogen, controls erosion of the topsoil, and produces lots of oxygen, considering how fast it grows. Furthermore, Hemp could be used to replace many potentially harmful products, such as tree paper (the process of which uses bleaches and other toxic chemicals, apart from contributing to deforestation), cosmetics (which often contain synthetic oils that can clog pores and provide little nutritional content for the skin), plastics (which are petroleum based and cannot decompose), and more.</body>
    </post> 
 <post id="MS_10340_40265545">
      <user id="MS_12394078">
        <username>Heavy Metal Pirate</username>
        <sex>M</sex>
        <age>20</age>
        <city>EVANSVILLE</city>
        <province>Indiana</province>
        <country>US</country>
      </user>
      <date>1206296520</date>
      <body>    The first American Flag was sown of hemp, and the original draft of the Constitution was written on Hemp paper.</body>
    </post> 
 <post id="MS_10340_40266228">
      <user id="MS_91947004">
        <username>uncle</username>
        <sex>M</sex>
        <age>52</age>
        <city>LAS VEGAS</city>
        <province>Nevada</province>
        <country>US</country>
      </user>
      <date>1206297240</date>
      <body>Not me. It's 17 miles to work... one way. 17 miles back all up hill. I ave to get up at 4:30am. No way do I want a sore ass and more lack of sleep.</body>
    </post> 
 <post id="MS_10340_40266326">
      <user id="MS_154281196">
        <username>Marcus</username>
        <sex>M</sex>
        <age>40</age>
        <city>San Diego</city>
        <province>California</province>
        <country>US</country>
      </user>
      <date>1206297360</date>
      <body>Actually, I gotta big dog. I can just slap a couple of commercial liscense plates on him and ride him to work. Don't think I haven't been considering it either. And how the hell do you explain the fact that Diesel fuel is the most expensive out of them all??? It's the most unrefined fuel on the market. It's junk fuel and it used to be a little more expensive than dirt! Now it's like gold! WTF???</body>
    </post> 
 <post id="MS_10340_40267851">
      <user id="MS_86264943">
        <username>robo to the rescue</username>
        <sex>M</sex>
        <age>18</age>
        <city>Heath/Newark</city>
        <province>Ohio</province>
        <country>US</country>
      </user>
      <date>1206299100</date>
      <body>Bringing back mass transit would be ideal. Filling up the average Semi costs $600.00, why not put that money back on the rails? It would take a long time to update the country, decades most likely, but the end result could/would be fantastic.</body>
    </post> 
 <post id="MS_10340_40268855">
      <user id="MS_2653008">
        <username>Poingly</username>
        <sex>F</sex>
        <age>104</age>
        <city>BROOKLYN</city>
        <province>New York</province>
        <country>US</country>
      </user>
      <date>1206300180</date>
      <body>I take the subway to work, it's great!</body>
    </post> 
 <post id="MS_10340_40271481">
      <user id="MS_347006598">
        <username>Cold Steal II</username>
        <sex>F</sex>
        <age>104</age>
        <city>CHICO</city>
        <province>California</province>
        <country>US</country>
      </user>
      <date>1206303360</date>
      <body>Kind of hard to ride a bike to work in California most people have to drive 20 to 60 miles one way to work. If you live in downtown NY, Chicago, Seatle or San Fransisco its possible but not most of the country</body>
    </post> 
 <post id="MS_10340_40284046">
      <user id="MS_110882268">
        <username>mrgone</username>
        <sex>M</sex>
        <age>52</age>
        <city>TUCKER</city>
        <province>Georgia</province>
        <country>US</country>
      </user>
      <date>1206332460</date>
      <body>  That sounds right. In the orginal 13 colonies if you had a farm or plantation, it was illegal to not grow hemp. But this gov't we have today does everything just the opposite of the founding fathers who's principles &amp; ideals made this country great. Look what these clowns are doing to it. I say we oust the bumbs Via that other great document called the Declaration of Independence.</body>
    </post> 
 <post id="MS_10340_40288817">
      <user id="MS_35008563">
        <username>Ashley *Loses a lot of e-fights*</username>
        <sex>F</sex>
        <age>23</age>
        <city>Mons</city>
        <province/>
        <country>BE</country>
      </user>
      <date>1206343860</date>
      <body>I always laughed at that suggestion when i was living in Missouri. I am NOT riding my bicycle 45 miles to work down a rural windy highway. People forget places still exist where you must go at least 30 miles to find a job. There was no town, just a stop sign on the pavement.</body>
    </post>
</posts> 
