<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_10326_40833337"> 
<user id ="MS_49758487"> 
	 <username>SSG Alexander VanArsdall</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>31</age> 
	 <city>In the sand</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>IQ</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1207163580</date> 
 <body>Believe me, guys, I'm very much a "take care of our own first" kinda guy. I firmly believe we should withdraw all forces from overseas, peaceful or otherwise. I don't see the need for 14 active Aircraft Carriers plus escorts, either. I also hate the fact that so much of our own economy is tied up in the world market, as well as the fact that we pay out billions in foreign aid when we've got people starving in the streets.  I'm a staunch isolationist; always have been.  However, what I like and don't like doesn't change the facts. I'm willing to make the sacrifices necessary to withdraw into our shells and take care of ourselves first, but I can't make that choice for the rest of the country (which is why I will never run for office). What's good for me isn't always good for everyone else.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10326_40834241"> 
<user id ="MS_334716808"> 
	 <username>Our countrys foundrs cherishd liberty nt democracy</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>NORTH LAS VEGAS</city> 
	 <province>Nevada</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1207164600</date> 
 <body>  So what he says in this video isn't true?        </body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10326_40834459"> 
<user id ="MS_49758487"> 
	 <username>SSG Alexander VanArsdall</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>31</age> 
	 <city>In the sand</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>IQ</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1207164780</date> 
 <body>   Next-Gen Nuke Subs and F-22s I'm okay with, although not nearly in the number we are building. We need to stay on top as far as conventional military technology is concerned, and I'm okay with a few wings of $130+ billion aircraft.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10326_40834572"> 
<user id ="MS_49758487"> 
	 <username>SSG Alexander VanArsdall</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>31</age> 
	 <city>In the sand</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>IQ</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1207164900</date> 
 <body>   The part about 700 bases in 130 countries is true, the rest is opinion.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10326_40835629"> 
<user id ="MS_50977157"> 
	 <username>Big Papi</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>28</age> 
	 <city>Vanlando</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>VA</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1207166220</date> 
 <body>  The Constitution doesn't give any president the power to rule the world.  That's true as well.  As for his opinions, a lot of them are favorable on the world stage.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10326_40836104"> 
<user id ="MS_118433906"> 
	 <username>MINARCHISM</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>25</age> 
	 <city>Greater Boston</city> 
	 <province>Massachusetts</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1207166820</date> 
 <body>Yes, despite all the aid the US gives out, which - by the way - is done on purpose as a bureacratic tool to get them to rely on us, they don't like us - and they want us out.  Popular world vote does NOT like the US policing the world, and despite how they act when we give them aid etc, it makes them rely on us, and in reality makes them despise us more. It's all about the pecking order, and the side effects of reliance - as opposed to independents. This also gets "misconstrued" as a forced feeling of inferiority, which is also unliked.  This is the general world opinion of the US.  Lets get the hell out, it will benefit everyone involved in the long run.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10326_40837049"> 
<user id ="MS_49758487"> 
	 <username>SSG Alexander VanArsdall</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>31</age> 
	 <city>In the sand</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>IQ</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1207168260</date> 
 <body>   Tell that to the United Nations. A HUGE majority of the relief and peacekeeping missions we are on, worldwide, are the result of UN mandate.  Do some research instead of spewing Ron Paul blogs.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10326_40838560"> 
<user id ="MS_118433906"> 
	 <username>MINARCHISM</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>25</age> 
	 <city>Greater Boston</city> 
	 <province>Massachusetts</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1207170960</date> 
 <body>Yay, more strawman arguments.  And spewing Ron Paul blogs?  Uhmmmm... buddy, despite what the UN is and does (which, in case you didnt know, is a multi-national collaborative entity BTW and is not made up solely of the US), that doesn't discredit the world's general opinion about the US.  Especially when the UN says, "No, you can't invade iraq", and the US says "Too bad, what are you going to do?" Sicne that IS basically how it went down.  The US government does what it wants, regardless of what the UN wants. The US only "abides" by the UN when it's convenient for them. It's a big fucking joke. So don't try and back the US and opinion with the collaborative effors of the UN - because then you just end up looking like a complete jackass.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10326_40838689"> 
<user id ="MS_3383949"> 
	 <username>mike (ron paul 2008)</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>29</age> 
	 <city>grayslake</city> 
	 <province>Illinois</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1207171200</date> 
 <body>  are you arguing that i should be responsible for subsidizing the germany economy?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10326_40838732"> 
<user id ="MS_3383949"> 
	 <username>mike (ron paul 2008)</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>29</age> 
	 <city>grayslake</city> 
	 <province>Illinois</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1207171260</date> 
 <body>  and we are morally superior to all and can print dolla dolla bills y'all. while most people still take them. military empires always end well</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>