<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_8974_41236495"> 
<user id ="MS_220905344"> 
	 <username>Capt.Yossarian</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>33</age> 
	 <city>Seattle</city> 
	 <province>Washington</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1207821480</date> 
 <body>   So what you are really saying is that poor people favor democrats. But if that was the case, why aren't the majority of poor white amaericans also democrat? Statistically more white people rely on social services than blacks.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8974_41236584"> 
<user id ="MS_220905344"> 
	 <username>Capt.Yossarian</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>33</age> 
	 <city>Seattle</city> 
	 <province>Washington</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1207821600</date> 
 <body>   Please explian why Reagan would choose to deliver his first campaign speech in Mississippi, at the urging of Trent Lott no less, a known bigot and racist.  This is exactly the kind of denial that the article talks about.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8974_41236749"> 
<user id ="MS_238935762"> 
	 <username>The Ogre.</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>68</age> 
	 <city>GREEN BAY</city> 
	 <province>Wisconsin</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1207821780</date> 
 <body> Don't forget the nice image of the black welfare queen that reagan so lovingly implanted in so many brains.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8974_41236752"> 
<user id ="MS_13948944"> 
	 <username>Nadya the Mexifail</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>21</age> 
	 <city>So not heading to the hills...DENIED!</city> 
	 <province>Texas</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1207821780</date> 
 <body>  If I remember correctly, the freedmen became sharecroppers and then moved to the cities when industry took off. And then industry left, leaving blacks in ghettos with no job skills in service.  If I am wrong, correct me. I slept 4 hours last night.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8974_41241790"> 
<user id ="MS_220905344"> 
	 <username>Capt.Yossarian</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>33</age> 
	 <city>Seattle</city> 
	 <province>Washington</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1207827360</date> 
 <body>Trent Lott once said, "The country would have been better off had segregationist candidate Strom Thurmond been voted into office."</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8974_41244967"> 
<user id ="MS_8793106"> 
	 <username>JP</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>28</age> 
	 <city>Chicago</city> 
	 <province>Illinois</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1207831380</date> 
 <body> Nah you said republicans as a blanket statement.  Black politicians take more advantage of their own race than anyone else. Jesse Jackson, Al Sharpton.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8974_41256313"> 
<user id ="MS_220905344"> 
	 <username>Capt.Yossarian</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>33</age> 
	 <city>Seattle</city> 
	 <province>Washington</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1207846560</date> 
 <body>  I didn't say all republicans are racist, what I said rather, was that the republican party has a history of racism. Also, the republican party is in denial about this and this is exactly why most blacks will not vote for a republican.  If you read the article, the author suggests that it is a good thing that Bush is reaching out to black voters finally, but it will not work until the republican party adresses it's racism in the past.  I've yet to hear a good reason for Reagan to deliver his initial campaign speech, repleat with overtones of states rights vs federal rights, in Philadelphia, MI, the exact town in which three civil rights workers were murdered in one of the 1960s' ugliest cases of racist violence. It was a ringing declaration of his support for "states' rights" — a code word for resistance to black advances clearly understood by white Southern voters.  If this wasn't race baiting, what was it? Please explain.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8974_41256844"> 
<user id ="MS_119052551"> 
	 <username>Carly</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>22</age> 
	 <city>LAKE WORTH</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1207847160</date> 
 <body> Good point...</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8974_41257304"> 
<user id ="MS_220905344"> 
	 <username>Capt.Yossarian</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>33</age> 
	 <city>Seattle</city> 
	 <province>Washington</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1207847700</date> 
 <body>  Thankyou. Where are all these Reagan Conservatives I keep hearing about? I really hope their silence on this topic is because they are all deep in contemplation, wrestling with their own inner demons.  I'll assume that.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8974_41257519"> 
<user id ="MS_12051898"> 
	 <username>Nory</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>U really wanna know?</city> 
	 <province>MARYLAND</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1207847940</date> 
 <body>  No, blacks were not given access to credit and property in the manner that whites were due to racism. In the 60's many black neighborhoods were destroyed to make the interstate highway system, the replacement was high density public housing. In 68, when king died blacks destroyed their own commercial centers, but these were OWNED by whites and rented to blacks. That was part of the anger, to this day most of these places are still just as they were after the riots. In combination with the drugs that were imported into the cities by Regean to destroy the black pride movement, these things destroyed confidence and morale in the black community, causing them to blame the man. Most of the children from the 70's grew up to be either cynical adults, or backstabbers to the ppl they left behind when they made it, like Barrack and Michelle Obama.</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>