<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42940120"> 
<user id ="MS_307029732"> 
	 <username>Aifo ani</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>69</age> 
	 <city>BRISTOW</city> 
	 <province>Virginia</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210641180</date> 
 <body>  And the Arab world isn't?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42940216"> 
<user id ="MS_307029732"> 
	 <username>Aifo ani</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>69</age> 
	 <city>BRISTOW</city> 
	 <province>Virginia</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210641480</date> 
 <body> The real Jew-Haters think that we Jews do not have a right to defend ourselves.Â  When you ask them what actions Israel could take that they woudl approve of, they pretend that they weren't asked.Â  Except, one, who siad that israel should give back the occupied territories (which worked so well with Gaza...).</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42940313"> 
<user id ="MS_307029732"> 
	 <username>Aifo ani</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>69</age> 
	 <city>BRISTOW</city> 
	 <province>Virginia</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210641900</date> 
 <body> Ehud:  We may have elected Bush twice but at least we didn't elect Gore (whom I voted for and am glad that he lost) or Kerry (who wanted Carter and Baker to be in charge of middle-east policy).  And Olmert has what, a 3% approval rating and you can't get rid of him? He is the architect of the disaster in Lebanon, the failure to take adequate steps against the Kassams, and a whole lot of bribery.  At least Bush's ratings are higher than congresses.  Both the Republcians and Democrats suck at energy policy..Â  Since the first oil embargo in 1973, America has done NOTHING about alternate (i.e. nuclear) energy.Â  I think they have been bribed by the Saudis (who paid for clinton's and Carter's libraries and hired James Baker III as a lobbyist).</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42940416"> 
<user id ="MS_107552026"> 
	 <username>*</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>76</age> 
	 <city>GL</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country></country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210642320</date> 
 <body>  oh yeah, gore certainly would have been a worseÂ president than bush. lol.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42942300"> 
<user id ="MS_138019879"> 
	 <username>Ehud</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>27</age> 
	 <city>Kibbutz Naan</city> 
	 <province>Central Israel</province> 
	 <country>IL</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210671120</date> 
 <body>   LMAO  Are you joking?  First off, Olmert's got a bad approval rating but doesn't quit. what am I supposed to do about it? assassinate him? grow up you turd. I voted for someone else (the Elders' party), won't vote for them again, and that's it.   now as for the US voting Dubyah in TWICE....   First off, both Gore and Kerry would have been better for the US and for the world. Hell, evenÂ  YOU would have made a better president (well, maybe not YOU but let's say... Shawn) In 20 years, Dubyah's gonna be recited in one breath with Hitler and Stalin and Mao, you dumbass... He's the worst thing that happened to the US since Vietnam  As if electing him once wasn't bad enough you actually were STUPID enough to repeat the same mistake TWICE... in a ROW...</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42946323"> 
<user id ="MS_164473103"> 
	 <username>Шагоход!</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>22</age> 
	 <city>Liberty City</city> 
	 <province>New York</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210678800</date> 
 <body>  Well you didn't vote for Olmert, that's big fact #1.  Conversely, something like 49.99999999999999999% of Americans didn't vote for Bush over Kerry.  Conversely, 50.0000112145246345645746734637% of Americans didn't vote for Bush over Gore.  So the ones who didn't vote for Bush are kind of in the same boat as you, with regards to unpopular leaders.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42949202"> 
<user id ="MS_307029732"> 
	 <username>Aifo ani</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>69</age> 
	 <city>BRISTOW</city> 
	 <province>Virginia</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210681680</date> 
 <body> I didn't say that you voted for Olmert.Â  No, you aren't supposed to assassinate Olmert. Or Livni.Â  All I said is that he is even more unpopular than Bush and Israel can't get rid of the sleeze.Â  He has too much protexia to give away to keep the Knesset from dumping him.  I only voted for Bush the second time.Â  The first time, I voted for Gore.Â   Gore and Kerry would have been worse than Bush - worse than Clinton even.Â  That is the opinion of the american public.Â  Obama would be a worldwide disaster as well.  Bush was a bad choice for president because:  * He can't speak off the cuff - a requirement for a national leader.  * He made Condi Rice Secretary of State.  * He hasn't released information on terrorism and the war in Iraq that would justify many of his actions.  The U.S. lost in Vietnam because the leftist press turned the country agaisnt the war, calling the Tet offensive a win for the NVA when it was a huge loss.Â  They are trying to do the same in Iraq.  If you want to know what is going on with the extreme left in the U.S., allow me to sendÂ you private messages.       To equate Bush with Hitler, Stalin and Mao is kind of nuts.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42969598"> 
<user id ="MS_113446481"> 
	 <username>Lisa :</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>18</age> 
	 <city>Hadera (finally)</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>IL</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210707000</date> 
 <body>  Well of course it is, but I'm saying that that other dude is blowing it wayy out of proportion. Its not like every country on earth is perfect.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42976199"> 
<user id ="MS_90278368"> 
	 <username>Rob</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>29</age> 
	 <city>Colchester</city> 
	 <province>East</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210717080</date> 
 <body>  I agree it would be nuts to equate Bush with either. All three were in control and were all brutal dictators. Bush is just a poor sap who's letting himself be lead along by the likes of Cheney and Rummy and their business interests. It would also be interesting to see how Bush Snr's company has done since the launch of this war on terror.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42982673"> 
<user id ="MS_138019879"> 
	 <username>Ehud</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>27</age> 
	 <city>Kibbutz Naan</city> 
	 <province>Central Israel</province> 
	 <country>IL</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210738500</date> 
 <body>Sorry, Rob History aims its darts at the man on top</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>