<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42926131"> 
<user id ="MS_113446481"> 
	 <username>Lisa :</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>18</age> 
	 <city>Hadera (finally)</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>IL</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210612620</date> 
 <body>  My claims? You, you Y-O-U.Â  are the one who has claimed all this stuff,  "America is "f" up. "America is a terrorist" "All America cares for is Israel and KSA" (+ all the swearing included) "Iraqis dislike Americans" ( I said some, you said who am I to judge, which can be inferred as you think all)  I'm just countering what you say. SoÂ whatever. I'll just leave to you spew more swear words.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42926167"> 
<user id ="MS_164473103"> 
	 <username>Шагоход!</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>22</age> 
	 <city>Liberty City</city> 
	 <province>New York</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210612680</date> 
 <body>Quote my bullshit then.  "Enlighten Me"</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42927355"> 
<user id ="MS_297467096"> 
	 <username>JDUB</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>28</age> 
	 <city>OKLAHOMA CITY</city> 
	 <province>Oklahoma</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210614780</date> 
 <body> Israel has the right to defend herself...</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42935100"> 
<user id ="MS_138019879"> 
	 <username>Ehud</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>27</age> 
	 <city>Kibbutz Naan</city> 
	 <province>Central Israel</province> 
	 <country>IL</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210627980</date> 
 <body>Wait wait...  2 Israelies... 5 Hamas militants....  where are all the dead oppressed palestinian children and women? where are those 30 to 1 rations gone to?  *cough*  that *pop* sound was my Sarcasm'o'meter blowing off the scale...   oh, and Lisa, the US is *f* up at some things... god knows, you people elected Dubyah... TWICE</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42939853"> 
<user id ="MS_107552026"> 
	 <username>*</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>76</age> 
	 <city>GL</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country></country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210640160</date> 
 <body>  i can proudly say, I never started a thread on the I/P-conflict (can't remember anyway)</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42940103"> 
<user id ="MS_307029732"> 
	 <username>Aifo ani</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>69</age> 
	 <city>BRISTOW</city> 
	 <province>Virginia</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210641120</date> 
 <body> Lisa:  We have been in Germany and Japan for 63 years, Korea for 58.  Do you support Obama whose foreign policy advisors are like a remake of Jimmy VCarters (except for Brezinzki who was Carter's adviosr?Â  then there is Powers, Mulloy (who resigned after it became public that he had been meeting with Hamas) and retired General Merril McPeake who blames Israel for the lack of peace.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42940120"> 
<user id ="MS_307029732"> 
	 <username>Aifo ani</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>69</age> 
	 <city>BRISTOW</city> 
	 <province>Virginia</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210641180</date> 
 <body>  And the Arab world isn't?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42940216"> 
<user id ="MS_307029732"> 
	 <username>Aifo ani</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>69</age> 
	 <city>BRISTOW</city> 
	 <province>Virginia</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210641480</date> 
 <body> The real Jew-Haters think that we Jews do not have a right to defend ourselves.Â  When you ask them what actions Israel could take that they woudl approve of, they pretend that they weren't asked.Â  Except, one, who siad that israel should give back the occupied territories (which worked so well with Gaza...).</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42940313"> 
<user id ="MS_307029732"> 
	 <username>Aifo ani</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>69</age> 
	 <city>BRISTOW</city> 
	 <province>Virginia</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210641900</date> 
 <body> Ehud:  We may have elected Bush twice but at least we didn't elect Gore (whom I voted for and am glad that he lost) or Kerry (who wanted Carter and Baker to be in charge of middle-east policy).  And Olmert has what, a 3% approval rating and you can't get rid of him? He is the architect of the disaster in Lebanon, the failure to take adequate steps against the Kassams, and a whole lot of bribery.  At least Bush's ratings are higher than congresses.  Both the Republcians and Democrats suck at energy policy..Â  Since the first oil embargo in 1973, America has done NOTHING about alternate (i.e. nuclear) energy.Â  I think they have been bribed by the Saudis (who paid for clinton's and Carter's libraries and hired James Baker III as a lobbyist).</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42940416"> 
<user id ="MS_107552026"> 
	 <username>*</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>76</age> 
	 <city>GL</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country></country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210642320</date> 
 <body>  oh yeah, gore certainly would have been a worseÂ president than bush. lol.</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>