<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42912167"> 
<user id ="MS_164473103"> 
	 <username>Шагоход!</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>22</age> 
	 <city>Liberty City</city> 
	 <province>New York</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210594200</date> 
 <body>  They seems to be the pet peeves of most people on this forum.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42912287"> 
<user id ="MS_347006598"> 
	 <username>Cold Steal II</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>104</age> 
	 <city>CHICO</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210594380</date> 
 <body>  and favorites</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42918747"> 
<user id ="MS_307029732"> 
	 <username>Aifo ani</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>69</age> 
	 <city>BRISTOW</city> 
	 <province>Virginia</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210602360</date> 
 <body> It will only increase when Iran has Hezbullaha nd Hamas start a new, imnproved (that is larger) war.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42924206"> 
<user id ="MS_113446481"> 
	 <username>Lisa :</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>18</age> 
	 <city>Hadera (finally)</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>IL</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210609680</date> 
 <body> Wow, I had no idea you were physic! While your at it, can you predict who is going to win the Elections, oh, and when America will pull out of Iraq?  I would just  love to know.   </body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42925264"> 
<user id ="MS_113446481"> 
	 <username>Lisa :</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>18</age> 
	 <city>Hadera (finally)</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>IL</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210611180</date> 
 <body>  McCain? You think McCain will win? I hope your wrong. I don't want to spend another 100 years in Iraq, nor do I support sombody who is buddy buddy with the lazy bum of a president we have.  To some Iraqis, we may be terrorists. But to us Americans, we are not terrorists. Its just how you view it. I don't agree with Iraq, I support pulling out, and taking care of our problems here. Besides, although our government is pretty much lazy and getting paid for doing nada, that does not mean that the rest of the country does not care. We do alot for the world, and we try to act out of morals and good hearts. I'm serious. We give aid to countries in need, we try to have a equal and fair country, we support values and good will, and we are very optimistic people. We try to be a good force in the world, even though it may not seem like it to you. I'm proud of this country and what it has done for the world, even though it has made some stupid mistakes. Such as this war. But, with all good comes the bad, and the in between. Nothing is perfect in life.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42925494"> 
<user id ="MS_164473103"> 
	 <username>Шагоход!</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>22</age> 
	 <city>Liberty City</city> 
	 <province>New York</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210611540</date> 
 <body>  Wait, the Iraqis (most of them) want the US to leave.  And most US troops think Iraq is a lost cause.  But you want more death.  Wow, youre pretty damn hateful.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42925663"> 
<user id ="MS_164473103"> 
	 <username>Шагоход!</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>22</age> 
	 <city>Liberty City</city> 
	 <province>New York</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210611840</date> 
 <body>  And I'm sure al-Sadr loves to bathe in the blood of the slain!  Seriously, it would be in everyone's best interest if the Iraqis were just left to their own devices.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42925789"> 
<user id ="MS_113446481"> 
	 <username>Lisa :</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>18</age> 
	 <city>Hadera (finally)</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>IL</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210612080</date> 
 <body>  Yes to some Iraqis, we may be terrorists and to some Iraqis we may not be. Who are you to decide that all Iraqis don't want us there? There must be some who are glad we got rid of Sadam . *This is not my personal oppinion, just common sense*  And you really don't need to swear. You keep on blabbing how you report people for saying the word "idiot" when you clearly say the F word. Twice. So I guess I should just report you for your dirty language. Hmm??  Nobody asked you to give a "s..." about us Americans. We don't need your "give a s." We have eachother, our pride, stability, and optimism. Who cares what in the world you think?  All our current government cares for is oil. All our future government will care about is God willing, Americans.  And also, those places are "s" holes to you, you probley have not visited them, thus you have no basis to call them "s" holes because you have no grounds to do so.  Andddd our country is not "f" up. Thats just what you think. And I'm sure most people could care less about wht you think when all you think is dirty words.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42925820"> 
<user id ="MS_164473103"> 
	 <username>Шагоход!</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>22</age> 
	 <city>Liberty City</city> 
	 <province>New York</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210612140</date> 
 <body>Alright, I won't quote you anymore.  It doesn't seem like you have anything better to say other than insults anyway.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11165_42926131"> 
<user id ="MS_113446481"> 
	 <username>Lisa :</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>18</age> 
	 <city>Hadera (finally)</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>IL</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1210612620</date> 
 <body>  My claims? You, you Y-O-U.Â  are the one who has claimed all this stuff,  "America is "f" up. "America is a terrorist" "All America cares for is Israel and KSA" (+ all the swearing included) "Iraqis dislike Americans" ( I said some, you said who am I to judge, which can be inferred as you think all)  I'm just countering what you say. SoÂ whatever. I'll just leave to you spew more swear words.</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>