<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_29636_44006588"> 
<user id ="MS_363214"> 
	 <username>Jason B™</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>28</age> 
	 <city>San Diego</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1212410580</date> 
 <body>The Brazilian Job: the follow up to Paramount’s US remake of The Italian Job is still on the cards, and it’s got a 2009 release date marked. Jason Statham, Mos Def, Mark Wahlberg and Charlize Theron are attached, as is director F Gary Gray.  I, Robot 2: All we know on this one is that it’s in the scripting stages still, with a potential 2010 release date planned in. No news on Mr Smith's involvement.  I Am Legend 2: Warner’s huge Christmas 2007 hit could also have a follow up, although it’d be interesting to see if Will Smith returned to it. A 2010 release date is also being mooted for this one.  Rest of the list is located below.   www.icanspeel.com</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29636_44006844"> 
<user id ="MS_243010948"> 
	 <username>Somebody</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>20</age> 
	 <city>Malmö</city> 
	 <province>Skåne län</province> 
	 <country>SE</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1212410880</date> 
 <body>Shrek 5? I didn't even know there was a fourth. X-D The last I saw was Shrek the Third. How could I missed Shrek 4?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29636_44007043"> 
<user id ="MS_60439146"> 
	 <username>El REY a.k.a. Da Franchise</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>25</age> 
	 <city>BRONX</city> 
	 <province>New York</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1212411060</date> 
 <body>a scary movie 5....why ?????  plz stop the madness, it was cool when the 1st one came out but @ 5m i thinks its time to put this franchise to rest</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29636_44007187"> 
<user id ="MS_379304382"> 
	 <username>stephanie</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>disappear in toronto</city> 
	 <province>Ontario</province> 
	 <country>CA</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1212411240</date> 
 <body>  agreed!  i hope the silent hill sequel is superior to the first.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29636_44007323"> 
<user id ="MS_2278378"> 
	 <username>Surf</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>27</age> 
	 <city>Riverside (No Longer San Diego :(</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1212411420</date> 
 <body>enough with the Saw's and Scary Movie sequels. Saw's aren't scary or gross and the Scary Movies havn't been funny since the 2nd one.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29636_44009691"> 
<user id ="MS_97326494"> 
	 <username>Duncan Destruction</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>25</age> 
	 <city>Dundee</city> 
	 <province>Scotland</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1212414240</date> 
 <body>  Shrek 4 was announced ages ago but animated movies usually take a couple of years to make so I think it comes out next year. The films have been that successful that they don't need to wait to see if the latest film does well before announcing another sequel.  Judging by the amount of sequels planned it seems that Hollywood is playing it safe.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29636_44011219"> 
<user id ="MS_284857110"> 
	 <username>dep</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>99</age> 
	 <city>Where the Horny Girls Aren't.</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1212415980</date> 
 <body>   I think it would be difficult for Mr. Smith to be in I Am Legend 2.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29636_44013062"> 
<user id ="MS_2278378"> 
	 <username>Surf</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>27</age> 
	 <city>Riverside (No Longer San Diego :(</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1212418380</date> 
 <body>  Yep, they should have went with the alternate ending if they wanted him for a sequel.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29636_44058872"> 
<user id ="MS_66539672"> 
	 <username>♥Mommykinsof4♥</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>34</age> 
	 <city>Boerne</city> 
	 <province>Texas</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1212493260</date> 
 <body>This is going to be very interesting!!  Silent Hill in my opinion was all I expected in a movie.. i have never played the games, but knew alot about the story...wonder where they are going to take this sequel!  Ace Ventura 3: oh please no!!!  The People Under The Stairs 2: wonder what made them after all these years to finally make a part 2.  The Untouchables: looking forward to this one!  Thought I heard a couple of years ago about Ghostship 2 being in post production? guess i heard wrong!</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29636_44059076"> 
<user id ="MS_141172136"> 
	 <username>annie</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>37</age> 
	 <city>ROCKAWAY</city> 
	 <province>New York</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1212493440</date> 
 <body>every one of them a waste of film...maybe The Untouchables prequel about the rise of Capone will be good...</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>