<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
 <post id="MS_9825_44094303">
      <user id="MS_149899577">
        <username>Pickett: Ha-Ha I Touched Your Heart</username>
        <sex>M</sex>
        <age>26</age>
        <city>salem</city>
        <province>Massachusetts</province>
        <country>US</country>
      </user>
      <date>1212547980</date>
      <body>Tue Jun 3, 5:00 PM ET    OTTAWA (Reuters) - U.S. soldiers who have deserted the military because of the war in Iraq should be allowed to stay permanently in Canada, the House of Commons voted in a nonbinding motion on Tuesday.  ADVERTISEMENT  The three opposition parties, which together hold a majority of seats in the House, backed a motion that said the government should allow conscientious objectors and their families "who have refused or left military service related to a war not sanctioned by the United Nations" to stay in Canada.  Canada was a haven for tens of thousands of draft dodgers during the Vietnam War and has attracted an estimated 175 to 200 Americans who are resisting the Iraq conflict.  "I think Canada has always been a place which has welcomed those who seek peace and seek freedom," Bob Rae, foreign affairs spokesman for the main opposition Liberal Party, told reporters outside the Commons after the vote.  The minority Conservative government opposes the idea, arguing that, unlike during the Vietnam War, the current U.S. military is composed of volunteers, and also that Washington allows people to apply for conscientious objector status.  "People do not join with their eyes closed. If they do, then they have their own problems," Conservative Member of Parliament Laurie Hawn, a retired lieutenant colonel in the Canadian Air Force, said during debate on the motion.  The Supreme Court of Canada refused last November to hear appeals of two U.S. deserters whose applications for refugee status had been turned down by immigration authorities.  (Reporting by Randall Palmer; editing by Rob Wilson)</body>
    </post> 
 <post id="MS_9825_44094423">
      <user id="MS_35280508">
        <username>LuCidiTy</username>
        <sex>F</sex>
        <age>46</age>
        <city>Alpha Centauri</city>
        <province/>
        <country>UM</country>
      </user>
      <date>1212548400</date>
      <body>Friendly!</body>
    </post> 
 <post id="MS_9825_44094447">
      <user id="MS_383137218">
        <username>Adolf</username>
        <sex>M</sex>
        <age>28</age>
        <city>Ontario</city>
        <province/>
        <country>CA</country>
      </user>
      <date>1212548460</date>
      <body>    It's all bullshit. It is high time we Canadians booted the cowardly assholes out of Canada. I don't want their kind in my country.</body>
    </post> 
 <post id="MS_9825_44094600">
      <user id="MS_35280508">
        <username>LuCidiTy</username>
        <sex>F</sex>
        <age>46</age>
        <city>Alpha Centauri</city>
        <province/>
        <country>UM</country>
      </user>
      <date>1212549000</date>
      <body>not so friendly.</body>
    </post> 
 <post id="MS_9825_44094621">
      <user id="MS_383137218">
        <username>Adolf</username>
        <sex>M</sex>
        <age>28</age>
        <city>Ontario</city>
        <province/>
        <country>CA</country>
      </user>
      <date>1212549060</date>
      <body>    Sweetie, it's my country, and I want the cowards out.</body>
    </post> 
 <post id="MS_9825_44094697">
      <user id="MS_35280508">
        <username>LuCidiTy</username>
        <sex>F</sex>
        <age>46</age>
        <city>Alpha Centauri</city>
        <province/>
        <country>UM</country>
      </user>
      <date>1212549300</date>
      <body>  calling them cowards is relying on a pretty narrow frame of reference, no?</body>
    </post> 
 <post id="MS_9825_44094787">
      <user id="MS_135055446">
        <username>Yadi</username>
        <sex>M</sex>
        <age>18</age>
        <city>Miami</city>
        <province>Florida</province>
        <country>US</country>
      </user>
      <date>1212549540</date>
      <body>I din't know Adolf owned Canada. Damn I need to read some books on current affairs.</body>
    </post> 
 <post id="MS_9825_44094811">
      <user id="MS_383137218">
        <username>Adolf</username>
        <sex>M</sex>
        <age>28</age>
        <city>Ontario</city>
        <province/>
        <country>CA</country>
      </user>
      <date>1212549600</date>
      <body>    They are cowards. Accept it. As such, they are not fit to be anywhere near my country.</body>
    </post> 
 <post id="MS_9825_44094918">
      <user id="MS_149899577">
        <username>Pickett: Ha-Ha I Touched Your Heart</username>
        <sex>M</sex>
        <age>26</age>
        <city>salem</city>
        <province>Massachusetts</province>
        <country>US</country>
      </user>
      <date>1212549900</date>
      <body>  to say the least the name fits him perfectly...to say the most it sounds like he woke with a hockey puck shoved up his ass</body>
    </post> 
 <post id="MS_9825_44100213">
      <user id="MS_6349493">
        <username>The Great Complexity.</username>
        <sex>M</sex>
        <age>24</age>
        <city>Dothan</city>
        <province>Alabama</province>
        <country>US</country>
      </user>
      <date>1212560820</date>
      <body>  Ahahahahahahha &lt;deep breathe&gt; ahahahahahahhaahaa  I don't know why but that made me laugh so effin hard.</body>
    </post>
</posts> 
