<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_28597_45638254"> 
<user id ="MS_595868"> 
	 <username>out of the cradle endlessly rocking</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>33</age> 
	 <city>East Los Angeles</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215022320</date> 
 <body>Dressed to Kill (or any DePalma).</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_28597_45638616"> 
<user id ="MS_103342454"> 
	 <username>Heidi</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>33</age> 
	 <city>Tampa</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215022740</date> 
 <body>American Psycho  Play Misty for Me  Memento  The Usual Suspects  Se7en  Rear Window  Silence of the Lambs</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_28597_45641481"> 
<user id ="MS_383726472"> 
	 <username>Baron ov Blood</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>23</age> 
	 <city>Six and a quarter Feet Under</city> 
	 <province>Illinois</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215026460</date> 
 <body>Almost anything by David Lynch. You can't really go wrong. Stuff like Blue Velvet, Mullholland Drive, Eraserhead, Wild At Heart, Lost Highway, Inland Empire. Look him up.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_28597_45643592"> 
<user id ="MS_383726472"> 
	 <username>Baron ov Blood</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>23</age> 
	 <city>Six and a quarter Feet Under</city> 
	 <province>Illinois</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215029640</date> 
 <body>Three more that came to mind....  The original Norweigan Insomnia  The original Dutch version of the Vanishing  Michael Haneke's Cache. Fantastic psychological thriller. If you're looking for challenging, than this is the movie for you.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_28597_45648034"> 
<user id ="MS_73639185"> 
	 <username>Rearranging the Deck Chairs</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>108</age> 
	 <city>FLORENCE</city> 
	 <province>Alabama</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215036960</date> 
 <body>  I'd recommend a couple of Hammer's little-known (or at least rarely mentioned) black and white suspense films, "Nightmare" and "Paranoiac".</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_28597_45648102"> 
<user id ="MS_390893579"> 
	 <username>Rip Van Willstein</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>31</age> 
	 <city>HUNTINGTON BEACH</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215037140</date> 
 <body>The Game  with Micheal Douglass and Sean Penn</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_28597_45650323"> 
<user id ="MS_138693636"> 
	 <username>zorrow</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>33</age> 
	 <city>US</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country></country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215042540</date> 
 <body>1.Cannibal Holocaust The film was banned in countless countries, and Deodato actually had to show evidence, in court, that the film was indeed fake, even going so far as to bring the actors on a popular TV talk show in Italy to prove they were still alive.  2. Men Behind the Sun To be honest, this film could be 100% fictional and it still would have made the top 10 list, as some of the scenes are downright brutal and extremely controversial: a (supposedly real) live cat is thrown into a room of starving rats and torn to pieces; a (supposedly real) corpse of a boy is slowly autopsied; a man is placed in a pressure chamber until his intestines blow out of his anus; a woman is tied to a post outside in the freezing cold, with buckets of cold water being dumped over her head to test the effects of frostbite, then her hands are plunged into boiling hot water, the skin peeling right off the bones; etc etc  3.Guinea Pig: Flower of Flesh and Blood The film itself is fairly simple: a creepy Japanese dude in a samurai suit (don’t ask us) kidnaps a girl, drugs her, ties her to a bed, and slowly cuts her to pieces. That’s it, that’s the whole movie. But the special effects are SO well done and so convincing, it really takes it to a whole other level. Fingers, hands, you name it; everything is cut off in slow, agonizing detail. The blood looks great, the gore is splendid, and the dismemberments are top notch (for example, after cutting off one of her hands, the fingers suddenly clench around his wrist, despite the fact it is no longer attached. Yikes.). 4. Cutting Moments Cutting Moments is a disquieting, harrowing look at the mental breakdown and subsequent downward spiral of a family torn apart by abuse, both physical and mental, and the limits of the human psyche. A mostly silent and slow-paced film, there’s no denying the talent behind Cutting Moments, as Buck masterfully lets silence speak louder then words; allowing the tension of the film to slowly rise to a boil before the incredibly disturbing and permanently scarring bloody climax.  5. Aftermath Aftermath pushes the boundaries of the genre in ways few films even dream of. Nacho Cerda made the film as part of a trilogy, focusing on death, post-death, and rebirth. Aftermath (the 2nd film in the trilogy) shows how we are all at the mercy of others once we die; our bodies nothing more then husks of meat to be poked, prodded, and disassembled.  DARE TO SEE THOSE MOVIE? MAIL ME IF U WANT THOSE MOVIE.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_28597_47143418"> 
<user id ="MS_43454654"> 
	 <username>moVin' vioLation</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>27</age> 
	 <city>Bumblef..$%</city> 
	 <province>New York</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217487240</date> 
 <body>  i watched DD for the first time yesterday. i wasn't impressed. it was ok but i don't understand the cult following that it has...</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_28597_47143773"> 
<user id ="MS_230705389"> 
	 <username>Lush O' the Irish</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>24</age> 
	 <city>OAK LAWN</city> 
	 <province>Illinois</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217487780</date> 
 <body>Seven was good Color of Night Copycat</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_28597_47144015"> 
<user id ="MS_43445330"> 
	 <username>相當 該死 RANDOM</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>26</age> 
	 <city>FORT WORTH</city> 
	 <province>Texas</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217488140</date> 
 <body>Silence Of The Lambs</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>