<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_30525_45749174"> 
<user id ="MS_381552302"> 
	 <username>sucker_angel</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>16</age> 
	 <city>-1</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>LV</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215217080</date> 
 <body>Mine favourite ending phrase is in "The Departed"  'OK'</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_30525_45749610"> 
<user id ="MS_137140976"> 
	 <username>Mr. Witness</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>22</age> 
	 <city>Sherman Oaks</city> 
	 <province>CALIFORNIA</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215219060</date> 
 <body>The gunfight in the graveyard at the end of THE GOOD, THE BAD, AND THE UGLY.  But that's not the end yet. Then Clint phucks with Tuco with the noose, the cross, the gold, and then "Hey, Blonde! You know what you are?".  Classic hands down-</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_30525_45750288"> 
<user id ="MS_97660171"> 
	 <username>Erik</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>27</age> 
	 <city>Aurora</city> 
	 <province>Illinois</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215222420</date> 
 <body>Also gotta love the ending to Monty Python's "Life of Brian" ...Always look on the bright side of life *whistles* I don't think that the Pythons have ever had an ending that wasn't funny...</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_30525_45750644"> 
<user id ="MS_97660171"> 
	 <username>Erik</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>27</age> 
	 <city>Aurora</city> 
	 <province>Illinois</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215223980</date> 
 <body>Both endings to Army of Darkness. The classic "S-Mart" ending and the Director's Cut "Apocalypse" Ending.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_30525_45753175"> 
<user id ="MS_19742420"> 
	 <username>Why so serious</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>38</age> 
	 <city>TULSA</city> 
	 <province>Oklahoma</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215232500</date> 
 <body>the end to the boondock saints....not the very end but the courtroom scene.    my personal fave...  jaws</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_30525_45753424"> 
<user id ="MS_388296446"> 
	 <username>Nick</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>18</age> 
	 <city>LARGO</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215233220</date> 
 <body>You cant talk about great movie endings without talking about "The Sting." shure it's lost it's "sting" now adays bacause it's commin knoledge and tons of movies have imataded that ending makeing it a bit cheshe, but when it came out, yhe audiance appaded the ending.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_30525_45768771"> 
<user id ="MS_358321294"> 
	 <username>Emergence</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>37</age> 
	 <city>Oregon</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215260400</date> 
 <body>The original "The Wicker Man"   THE 1973 ORIGINAL VERSION NOT the Remake.     I didn't see the remake but Im going to assume this was the ending:  Nicholas Cage jumps out of the wicker man at the last moment that its burning, performs Krag Maga on the village leader and several of the other pagans, disarming his gun taking it and grabbing the girl, Nick C. then gets into a car for a long car chase sequence with villagers in pursuit in their cars, with a hail of bullets following him, he crashes through a random fruit stand. Drives under a semi-truck, turning the car into a convertable, the cars following him crash into it. Then he slams into a firetruck which explodes. It seems like all is lost as the pagans surround a bruised and tattered and burned Nick Cage trapped in his car. Then the sound of helicopter blades:  Miraculously the ATF shows up in helicopters. ATF paratroupers leap out on rope ladders. The ATF burns the entire town to the ground like Waco. At the end of the movie a battlescarred Nickolas Cage, exhausted out of breath, gets praised by the leading ATF Commander (who is also Nick's dad) something like "Good job son, sorry I doubted you in Waco"   Then the credits roll, and some lame rap music plays with these lyrics: "Wicka, wicka, wicka; my n$gga, n$gga, n$gga"</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_30525_45768868"> 
<user id ="MS_67832205"> 
	 <username>THE DzA â˜®[happy]</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>20</age> 
	 <city>FRESNO</city> 
	 <province>CALIFORNIA</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215260520</date> 
 <body>Enemy at the gates</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_30525_45769556"> 
<user id ="MS_117412665"> 
	 <username>The Ninja formerly known as James</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>32</age> 
	 <city>BELLEVUE</city> 
	 <province>NEBRASKA</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215261600</date> 
 <body>  Only Monty Python would think of ending a movie with a musical number with a bunch of dudes on crosses. :)</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_30525_45769752"> 
<user id ="MS_147819654"> 
	 <username>Sir-Lionhart(Loves asian girl)</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>17</age> 
	 <city>MILWAUKEE</city> 
	 <province>Wisconsin</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1215261840</date> 
 <body>When the guy got the girl at the end of that one movie.</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>