<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_28397_46338927"> 
<user id ="MS_74943305"> 
	 <username>Retrocadia</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>33</age> 
	 <city>Arlington</city> 
	 <province>Texas</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216203360</date> 
 <body>   Well Mr. Allen, I can't really disagree with you. I'm a TF Fanboy myself. I think I feel a bit of excitement, but that could be anxiety and worry over how bad it might be ruined even more. Instead of a magical cube that they all sprouted up from, they might create some other magical ooze that the cube sprang from without any answers to any questions.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_28397_46339506"> 
<user id ="MS_43445330"> 
	 <username>ç›¸ç•¶ è©²æ­» RANDOM</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>26</age> 
	 <city>FORT WORTH</city> 
	 <province>Texas</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216204020</date> 
 <body>I just read that have told Megan Fox to Gain 10 Pounds for Transformers Sequel.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_28397_46340636"> 
<user id ="MS_165864578"> 
	 <username>C. Allen Bell</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>108</age> 
	 <city>South philadelphia</city> 
	 <province>Pennsylvania</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216205220</date> 
 <body>where at? Boobs, behind?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_28397_46340872"> 
<user id ="MS_43445330"> 
	 <username>ç›¸ç•¶ è©²æ­» RANDOM</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>26</age> 
	 <city>FORT WORTH</city> 
	 <province>Texas</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216205520</date> 
 <body>Good question...  </body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_28397_46344413"> 
<user id ="MS_109505553"> 
	 <username>Ivo =/</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>18</age> 
	 <city>Bradenton</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216209120</date> 
 <body></body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_28397_46404512"> 
<user id ="MS_127457269"> 
	 <username>Shawn</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>37</age> 
	 <city>Michigan</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216297320</date> 
 <body>What really ruined The Transformers movie is the fact that Michael Bay is not a fan of the transformers, and he stated he did'nt want to make a cartoon of the Transformers, The Transformations were to complex, the transformations of the Transformers from past shows were never complex, they were promoting stuff that took away space for putting more information in the script ( Like Mountain Dew, X-Box, ect. ), They had one of the Original voice actors ( Optimus Prime ( AKA Petter Cullen ), and not the other ( Frank Welker ( AKA Megatron ), Way tomany quotes slaming the original series, Not having Bumblebee a VW bug, and yet having a VW bug in the movie!, none of the desgins looked anything near the original desgins of the Transformers, Not having the Matrix Of Leadership, and instead we get some stupid cube ( Hey was'nt the cube in one of the later Transformers shows ), Bay and Hasbro TRANSFORMED this movie in to a pile of crap! ( Anyone feel free to add the transfomation sound effect! ), the whole witwikey background story, and the selling of his gradfathers glasses could have been deleted, and something better put in, I only payed $2.00 to see Transformers, and to be frank it's not even worth $2.00, that would be an insult to the movies that deserve the admition price of $2.00 LOL!</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_28397_46404608"> 
<user id ="MS_109505553"> 
	 <username>Ivo =/</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>18</age> 
	 <city>Bradenton</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216297380</date> 
 <body>I wanted Frank Welker in that movie.  What in the FUCK were they thinking?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_28397_46404900"> 
<user id ="MS_59766340"> 
	 <username>My name..Oh yes. I have it written somewhere.</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>27</age> 
	 <city>BRONX</city> 
	 <province>New York</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216297680</date> 
 <body>Have you played the game or watched how it looks when you hear franks voice with megatron footage?  It doesn't work.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_28397_46404915"> 
<user id ="MS_23964149"> 
	 <username>Rockstar Cowboy</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>26</age> 
	 <city>Golden</city> 
	 <province>Colorado</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216297740</date> 
 <body>  And told her to come over to my house.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_28397_46404960"> 
<user id ="MS_109505553"> 
	 <username>Ivo =/</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>18</age> 
	 <city>Bradenton</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216297740</date> 
 <body>  Yes  I like it better for some reason.</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>