<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_9463_46344014"> 
<user id ="MS_137561496"> 
	 <username>Robert</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>62</age> 
	 <city>Stirling</city> 
	 <province>Ontario</province> 
	 <country>CA</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216208760</date> 
 <body>Gas prices in Ontario dropped from 1.38/l to 1.274/l over the last month. They are now back up to about 1.345/l. That works out to about U.S. $6.00/gal.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9463_46344846"> 
<user id ="MS_116715560"> 
	 <username>Limpin like a Rockstar</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>22</age> 
	 <city>Scho. B.</city> 
	 <province>Hawaii</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216209540</date> 
 <body>Of course, gas prices goes down when I can't drive my car...damned broken foot.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9463_46352125"> 
<user id ="MS_339094582"> 
	 <username>Jack White</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>38</age> 
	 <city>Campton</city> 
	 <province>Kentucky</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216217700</date> 
 <body> Happy Califrnia your gas have been to high already in Kentucky they,ve gone up 20 cents in past 2 weeks but we are still only at $4.04 a gallon.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9463_46360429"> 
<user id ="MS_19946542"> 
	 <username>Mr. Cheap Cigar</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>31</age> 
	 <city>Los Angeles</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216228140</date> 
 <body>  Maybe everything is just evening out, then. A few weeks ago I paid $4.79 a gallon at the gas station by my house and yesterday I paid $4.53 a gallon at the same place. And I noticed at some places downtown it was even ten cents cheaper.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9463_46473920"> 
<user id ="MS_218632225"> 
	 <username>Chupacabre</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>AUBURN</city> 
	 <province>Indiana</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216397760</date> 
 <body>Who knows, but I do find more and more people standing at the gas pump curseing with me as they fill their vehicles.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9463_46478036"> 
<user id ="MS_8225318"> 
	 <username>dujac</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>49</age> 
	 <city>Hot Springs</city> 
	 <province>Arkansas</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216404060</date> 
 <body>world demand for expensive gasoline has decreased  if demand reamains low, prices will drop</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9463_46481327"> 
<user id ="MS_335313387"> 
	 <username>Ryan</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>23</age> 
	 <city>EUGENE</city> 
	 <province>Oregon</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216409160</date> 
 <body>Thanks for that nugget of brilliance Dujac. To expound and make a predictive statement on that, Chinese subsidies and such are due to drop significantly after the Olympics. So, you should probably see a quick jump up in oil during the Olympics, and then a drop that will continue as world demand stays low.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9463_46483853"> 
<user id ="MS_64355192"> 
	 <username>Jason</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>25</age> 
	 <city>Missouri</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216413420</date> 
 <body>I know why. There's a presidential election coming up. Bush lifts the off shore drilling ban and prices fall a bit. Makes republicans look good. The oil companies need another Republican president so they can continue raping your wallets. Don't fall for it. And don't worry, gas prices haven't topped off. Not by a long shot.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9463_46489286"> 
<user id ="MS_44198047"> 
	 <username>mê£äñìê</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>26</age> 
	 <city>Small Town</city> 
	 <province>Colorado</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216426260</date> 
 <body> If you think the oil companies are seeking a Republican President in the house this next election you are absolutely correct. If a Democrat happens to step in to the roll of President the price of fuel will increase. A Democratic President will raise taxes on fuel, making prices sky rocket.  You think prices are hitting you bank account hard now, just wait and see what will happen if a Democrat takes over as commander and chief. You think filling your car now is expensive, just watch and see.. You may be shocked at the outcome.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9463_46490869"> 
<user id ="MS_102902297"> 
	 <username>Jr.</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>28</age> 
	 <city>ILLINOIS</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216430940</date> 
 <body>Gas prices did go down. Or better said, the gas guzzlers went down south... of the border.   The US and Mexican press had a field day sensationalizing the events for several months, which in turn greatly affected tourism and Baja’s economy as over 40 percent of the Baja coastal region depends on tourism. Baja has experienced the economic pain that also punctuates for them the great binational economic interdependence.  Now it seems that despite the media fervor in reporting and sensationalizing Mexico’s problems with drug capos, Americans are flocking back to Baja. Why?  Saving money, trumps fear. Gasoline prices now over $4.50 a gallon in San Diego is available anywhere in Baja for around $2.55 a gallon. And the stampede of US trucks buying diesel fuel at $2.20 a gallon versus over $5 a gallon in San Diego, has caught Baja shorthanded an unable to keep up with the demand. Once again the economic interdependence is evident.  Robert Kline from Orange County waiting to fuel up his Ford pickup said that once he began reading and seen on nightly news about all the cars crossing for gas, he figured things can’t be that bad, so he decided to come back to Baja that was his favorite weekend retreat. Like Kline, others are beginning to see that things are OK, and they too will begin to travel to Baja. So things will go back to normal during the summer months.  http://hispanicvista.com/HVC/Columnist/posiojr/070608Patrick_Osi o.htm  BTW Mexico's gas prices go up only by inflation rate, where here in the US they are set by the individual sellers (companies).</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>