<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_29071_46825875"> 
<user id ="MS_141172136"> 
	 <username>annie</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>37</age> 
	 <city>ROCKAWAY</city> 
	 <province>New York</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216980780</date> 
 <body> Yeah...we should have kept ignoring him...it would drive him crazy in a couple of days</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29071_46826038"> 
<user id ="MS_118204420"> 
	 <username>Dain bramaged</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>29</age> 
	 <city>The last place you look</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216980960</date> 
 <body> yeah b/c if you're on a computer that=inside. welcome to 2008 dude I'm on my laptop @ school, outside.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29071_46826618"> 
<user id ="MS_23674260"> 
	 <username>=JAIME= (GABBA GABBA HEY)</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>Florida</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1216981560</date> 
 <body> i dont' want anyone saying this movie is cheesy until they see the original with Adam West... I shudder at the thought -_-  Besides.. Super Heroes are cheesy. They are grown men who wear skin tight costumes and underwear on the outside that can fly and have super strength. It doesn't matter how awesome you make a super hero movie, the premise is still cheesy.  But I loves the super heroes :)</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29071_46874340"> 
<user id ="MS_321842614"> 
	 <username>Alan</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>99</age> 
	 <city>Newcastle</city> 
	 <province>Northeast</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217063340</date> 
 <body>  Yep. Mawkishness is running riot in the US at the moment. Ledger will win an Oscar because of is untimely death rather than his role and that is actually rather insulting to his memory, in my opinion.  A.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29071_46875061"> 
<user id ="MS_181966732"> 
	 <username>Clif</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>Sunset Beach</city> 
	 <province>Georgia</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217064480</date> 
 <body>  u really hate the fact ppl loved the movie don't you?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29071_46875558"> 
<user id ="MS_181966732"> 
	 <username>Clif</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>Sunset Beach</city> 
	 <province>Georgia</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217065200</date> 
 <body>  and don't say the movie is "ok" like it's a common fact.. all fanboy shit aside there are ppl you thought the movie was phenomenal. and johnnie u really are the last one to talk about ppl getting out more when all u do was bitch and moan. u are intitled to ur opinion. but all day long u bitch and moan about how all ppl do criticize u for ur opinion when a lot of them are trying understand wht u meant....What u just wrote was an insult.  (and coming from someone who found mamma mia better than this shouldn't really be talking :P)  /end thread  don't like the movie fine, great, w/e,. u don't like being criticized all the time about the subject then gtfo of the conversation quit jumping in the pool of ppl who loved the movie and yell out "the movie wasn't that great!", ur gonna get feedback  l8ter</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29071_46886839"> 
<user id ="MS_30647797"> 
	 <username>Lord Kalvin</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>23</age> 
	 <city>HOUSTON</city> 
	 <province>Texas</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217081640</date> 
 <body></body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29071_46890295"> 
<user id ="MS_43445330"> 
	 <username>相當 該死 RANDOM</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>26</age> 
	 <city>FORT WORTH</city> 
	 <province>Texas</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217087100</date> 
 <body>  Oh an your obsession with Friday The 13th ain't any different?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29071_46950535"> 
<user id ="MS_30647797"> 
	 <username>Lord Kalvin</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>23</age> 
	 <city>HOUSTON</city> 
	 <province>Texas</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217190000</date> 
 <body>lol, I agree that the fanboyism is lame, but so is pompous, "My taste in movies is better than yours" attitudes lol. How is that any different than what the fan boys do? Fighting over the internet is the ultimate in lame anyway haha, it's just like they say:  "Fighting over the internet is like racing in the special olympics... Even if u win, ur still retarded." ~Anonymous  Lol, Im all for intelligent discussions/debates... but the personal attacks are usually a clear sign of ignorance.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29071_46951123"> 
<user id ="MS_81580721"> 
	 <username>~Andy~</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>20</age> 
	 <city>Somewhere</city> 
	 <province>Tennessee</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217191080</date> 
 <body>C. Allen...Oder of the P10..... You two just made me have a seizure with you DPs. It's like looking into the eyes of the snake on Jungle Book.</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>