<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47002619"> 
<user id ="MS_2278378"> 
	 <username>Surf</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>27</age> 
	 <city>Riverside (No Longer San Diego :(</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217272740</date> 
 <body>  I suppose that would be true if you're a rapist. Us norms already know women are nuts.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47002634"> 
<user id ="MS_3420865"> 
	 <username>thatDUDEchris</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>24</age> 
	 <city>RANCHO CUCAMONGA</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217272740</date> 
 <body>a chubby hahhahahah</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47003759"> 
<user id ="MS_97912601"> 
	 <username>Dado</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>25</age> 
	 <city>Boise</city> 
	 <province>Idaho</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217274240</date> 
 <body>That movie had a million plot holes. Like they guy who gets killed in the bath tub. Why did he not freak out when he saw that girl again? Did he really think she wanted to hook up after what he done to her?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47006002"> 
<user id ="MS_115091385"> 
	 <username>Mark</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>40</age> 
	 <city>CHICAGO</city> 
	 <province>ILLINOIS</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217277660</date> 
 <body>  Did you watch the whole film? It's obvious why he went back with her. He's an idiot rapist! Many rapists actually believe their victims want to be raped. He felt she liked it and was coming back for seconds, or would that be fourths or fifths? She convinced him when she shot at him one minute, then relinquished the gun. Like I said, he's a freakin' idiot. Who the fuck would even do that to another person in the first place?  This was the uncut version I believe, and I got it from Netflix.  Glad I could entertain you Heidi, I'm a regular Roger Ebert! lol  But seriously, where are all the black movie reviewers? Roger is an honorary brother, but I think I'm going to send in an application.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47204147"> 
<user id ="MS_115091385"> 
	 <username>Mark</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>40</age> 
	 <city>CHICAGO</city> 
	 <province>ILLINOIS</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217573940</date> 
 <body>  Are there any drive-ins left in America?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47278030"> 
<user id ="MS_64042473"> 
	 <username>Ecirtap</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>99</age> 
	 <city>New Jersey</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217687640</date> 
 <body>There is one in NJ that I know of and I think there is still one in PA and CA. Not sure about anywhere else. I love drive ins? Loved this movie, revenge is a bitch. I saw it years ago and this was the first film I saw where a woman just fucked her attackers up. Loved that!!! Glad you watched it again. I told you :)</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47342819"> 
<user id ="MS_115091385"> 
	 <username>Mark</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>40</age> 
	 <city>CHICAGO</city> 
	 <province>ILLINOIS</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217793660</date> 
 <body>You were correct miss lady! As I reflect back on it, I did find it somewhat disturbing that she allowed the mentally challenged dude to have sex with her before killing him. Did she feel sorry for him and did not want him to die a virgin? I get getting naked with the lead dude to castrate him in the tub, but the hanging thing didn't really make sense. I thought she did it to make it look like a suicide at first, but nope.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47345479"> 
<user id ="MS_320148833"> 
	 <username>â˜ Jennâ˜ </username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>28</age> 
	 <city>SACRAMENTO</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217797500</date> 
 <body>  We have on in Sac thats been open 20+ years. Its closing after summer :(</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47345546"> 
<user id ="MS_320148833"> 
	 <username>â˜ Jennâ˜ </username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>28</age> 
	 <city>SACRAMENTO</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217797620</date> 
 <body>  Werent all the killings done in a sexual way? I think thats what makes the movie more unique and twisted.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47346662"> 
<user id ="MS_115091385"> 
	 <username>Mark</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>40</age> 
	 <city>CHICAGO</city> 
	 <province>ILLINOIS</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217799480</date> 
 <body>Another one bites the dust huh. Too bad. Going to the drive in as a kid was such fun. Glad to hear there is still one in NJ. And the last two murders weren't sexual really. She didn't have to get naked at all! And I am torn, should I have been happy or sad that she didn;t get naked.</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>