<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47000019"> 
<user id ="MS_3420865"> 
	 <username>thatDUDEchris</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>24</age> 
	 <city>RANCHO CUCAMONGA</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217269860</date> 
 <body>nice i have a dvd planet by my house and they have a bunch of these old cult type horror joints im see if i can find it there...cuz im not sure my video store will have this one...</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47001329"> 
<user id ="MS_393218373"> 
	 <username>Astro-Creep</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>18</age> 
	 <city>NEW YORK,</city> 
	 <province>New York</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217271120</date> 
 <body>Meh  Netflix will definately have them   Or just download Utorrent and find the films via torrent and watch them on the good old compy or put them on DVD :)   That's what i'm gonna do with the one i'm Downloading, because i cant find them over here and plus side one of them ain't even on DVD release, which is Silent Night Deadly Night 3.  Juss download and burn to dvd :)</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47002215"> 
<user id ="MS_64197263"> 
	 <username>FightAgainstFascism</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>25</age> 
	 <city>LAS VEGAS</city> 
	 <province>Nevada</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217272260</date> 
 <body>They showed this in drive-ins? Damn america sure has changed in 20 years.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47002440"> 
<user id ="MS_158512037"> 
	 <username>ζΩΜβΙε</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>34</age> 
	 <city>βμττ§εχ³</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>YE</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217272500</date> 
 <body>I was 11 or 12 when I first and last saw this.  I think it was the first full frontal I'd ever seen. I vaguely remember gettin a chubby.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47002619"> 
<user id ="MS_2278378"> 
	 <username>Surf</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>27</age> 
	 <city>Riverside (No Longer San Diego :(</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217272740</date> 
 <body>  I suppose that would be true if you're a rapist. Us norms already know women are nuts.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47002634"> 
<user id ="MS_3420865"> 
	 <username>thatDUDEchris</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>24</age> 
	 <city>RANCHO CUCAMONGA</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217272740</date> 
 <body>a chubby hahhahahah</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47003759"> 
<user id ="MS_97912601"> 
	 <username>Dado</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>25</age> 
	 <city>Boise</city> 
	 <province>Idaho</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217274240</date> 
 <body>That movie had a million plot holes. Like they guy who gets killed in the bath tub. Why did he not freak out when he saw that girl again? Did he really think she wanted to hook up after what he done to her?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47006002"> 
<user id ="MS_115091385"> 
	 <username>Mark</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>40</age> 
	 <city>CHICAGO</city> 
	 <province>ILLINOIS</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217277660</date> 
 <body>  Did you watch the whole film? It's obvious why he went back with her. He's an idiot rapist! Many rapists actually believe their victims want to be raped. He felt she liked it and was coming back for seconds, or would that be fourths or fifths? She convinced him when she shot at him one minute, then relinquished the gun. Like I said, he's a freakin' idiot. Who the fuck would even do that to another person in the first place?  This was the uncut version I believe, and I got it from Netflix.  Glad I could entertain you Heidi, I'm a regular Roger Ebert! lol  But seriously, where are all the black movie reviewers? Roger is an honorary brother, but I think I'm going to send in an application.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47204147"> 
<user id ="MS_115091385"> 
	 <username>Mark</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>40</age> 
	 <city>CHICAGO</city> 
	 <province>ILLINOIS</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217573940</date> 
 <body>  Are there any drive-ins left in America?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_29389_47278030"> 
<user id ="MS_64042473"> 
	 <username>Ecirtap</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>99</age> 
	 <city>New Jersey</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1217687640</date> 
 <body>There is one in NJ that I know of and I think there is still one in PA and CA. Not sure about anywhere else. I love drive ins? Loved this movie, revenge is a bitch. I saw it years ago and this was the first film I saw where a woman just fucked her attackers up. Loved that!!! Glad you watched it again. I told you :)</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>