<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47693838"> 
<user id ="MS_369060867"> 
	 <username>Frequency 13</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>104</age> 
	 <city>ATLANTA</city> 
	 <province>Georgia</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218312840</date> 
 <body>anybody bother by the fact mccain is "learning to get online" that is even a few steps down from bushes "one of the things i've used on the google is to pull up maps"  not that i'm some big obama fan but isn't it time we have a president that is at least mildly computer literate?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47694746"> 
<user id ="MS_395538055"> 
	 <username>Norseman</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>46</age> 
	 <city>MINNEAPOLIS</city> 
	 <province>Minnesota</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218314340</date> 
 <body>They got people for that.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47695327"> 
<user id ="MS_369060867"> 
	 <username>Frequency 13</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>104</age> 
	 <city>ATLANTA</city> 
	 <province>Georgia</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218315120</date> 
 <body> well "they" have "people" for everything...so why even care who gets elected? lets just vote in a retarded paraplegic cat. or to quote Burroughs, "A$$hole doesn't know what buttons to push or what happens when you push them" seriously here we have a guy who can pass laws to that effect the internet and doesn't even know how to get on it and i'm willing to bet he can't find the power button on his computer either, but we got people for that. i would just like to think that who ever gets elected is a bit worldly, a renaissance man or woman if you will and so living in our tech driven world understand something about it. its not like i'm asking for the president to be some macrovision drm breaker, just to at LEAST know how to get online.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47695537"> 
<user id ="MS_29433620"> 
	 <username>The Sentry</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>38</age> 
	 <city>Gold Country</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218315420</date> 
 <body>Hahahaha. This thread is funny.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47697108"> 
<user id ="MS_395242946"> 
	 <username>JAMES</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>60</age> 
	 <city>PITTSBURGH</city> 
	 <province>Pennsylvania</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218318120</date> 
 <body>  Indeed they do. You're never seen a puter in the Oval Office.  But you'd have to expect that anyone who is the least bit curious about anything, and wants to see what's really out there besides what is digested by staff, would have a desktop in the private office off the Oval.  Also a desktop for notes, e-mail, and writing, especially while in transit.  You would expect that with IT so critical to the economy and national security, the Commander-In-Chief would have at least a nodding acquaintance with hacks, viruses, broadband, and such.  He should also know that CERT is not a breath mint.  If there is a generation gap between the majority of the people and Senator McCain, this is another telling example.  And if this is just a continuation of the incuriosity, inattention, and vincible ignorance of the current president, so much the worse.  "What color is the red phone?" -- George W. Bush</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47700268"> 
<user id ="MS_195642716"> 
	 <username>Æon</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>26</age> 
	 <city>ΓΦΔΞΘΘξς</city> 
	 <province>Omniverse</province> 
	 <country>VA</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218324840</date> 
 <body>Another reason why a Rock would make a better president than McLame.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47702955"> 
<user id ="MS_395538055"> 
	 <username>Norseman</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>46</age> 
	 <city>MINNEAPOLIS</city> 
	 <province>Minnesota</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218332760</date> 
 <body>Thats crazy talk Iam sure Mccaine knows how to run basic programs and the internet,You younger people in your twentys that grew up on computers have a hard time beleaving that some people as old as Mccaine probably dont really have a want or need for computers.I know his daughter is the one who runs his election site. I have met alot young of people that dont like PCs and really have a desire to use them. If an executive of a major corperation asks for a document or information, do you really think hes going to sit down at a PC and get it himself? or make one of the people they pay to do it?.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47704461"> 
<user id ="MS_395242946"> 
	 <username>JAMES</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>60</age> 
	 <city>PITTSBURGH</city> 
	 <province>Pennsylvania</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218338340</date> 
 <body>  Have you ever been in a CEO's office? Or a VP's office?  Why not visit one soon?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47709420"> 
<user id ="MS_369060867"> 
	 <username>Frequency 13</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>104</age> 
	 <city>ATLANTA</city> 
	 <province>Georgia</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218350640</date> 
 <body> when the information is on a shared drive or within grasp of their computer for them to get? well ever executive i have known has done so. when it is down the hall being typed by his secretary on a royal typewriter, than no, they do usually send for it...or they send an *gasp* and email asking if someone could email them back the document·which in mccains case he would have to get his wife to come in and help him with</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47717308"> 
<user id ="MS_395242946"> 
	 <username>JAMES</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>60</age> 
	 <city>PITTSBURGH</city> 
	 <province>Pennsylvania</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218364020</date> 
 <body>  Wow. A blast from the past. I remember typewriters.  For skool I had a Smith-Corona and then an Olympia portable, plus one of the first Selectrics, ensconced in student publications offices.  The skool paper set its type every night on Justowriters, which were almost as noisy as pavement breakers.  In my first job I had a Remington manual, then an Olympia manual with more enameled sheet steel than a small fridge.  In the next job, everyone had IBM Selectrics.  Then down the chain to an IBM Executive, with type bars.  The next shop had correcting Selectrics, until the owner bought me a DECmate for Christmas.  Then secretaries became an endangered species.  And middle-aged, highly placed people had to learn how to type.  My heart bled for them.</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>