<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_3149_48053069"> 
<user id ="MS_21364047"> 
	 <username>Wing-man</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>22</age> 
	 <city>US</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country></country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218883800</date> 
 <body>I think men and women are mostly equal, but woman usually don't have as much power as men because of three things:   1: Woman are more likely to have less time to gain rank, they spend more time on education, family, etc. and they spend more money, money = time lost.  2: Woman are less likely to use force in order to get what they want.  3: Woman care about other peoples' feelings too much, they are less likely to get rid of people who are in their way.  Basically the percentage of woman who "play nice" is higher than the percentage of men who do. Also they focus on education more than men. (the education system actually tends to hold people back in life --- it's hard to prove due to the fact that the corporations think otherwise, without corp./gov. backing it would be obvious though.)</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_3149_48103470"> 
<user id ="MS_40204932"> 
	 <username>QS of the Si$terhood</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>24</age> 
	 <city>Georgetown</city> 
	 <province>Kentucky</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218974580</date> 
 <body>I don't believe that women and men are equal, it is something women are still trying to strive towards this very day.  I don't think it is a matter of time, education or "playing nice" but rather lack of experience and setting a higher bar for oneself (demand more). Women need to be more demanding and stand up for what they believe in. There is nothing wrong with having your voice heard or making a man serve you.  In ancient times it was a common thing to have men for slaves, ones that worshipped their goddess. By demanding more from men and holding that power that we truly have but have lost over time (threw greedy white men) it is a matter of regaining and utilizing what we have inside of us.  Being in control doesn't always have to be associated with bdsm or even being a control freak. Control, domination and power can come in many levels. It is a matter of what you want out of your own life and using what you are comfortable with.  All in all, be yourself!</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_3149_48113227"> 
<user id ="MS_377165218"> 
	 <username>Max</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>17</age> 
	 <city>Michigan</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218987960</date> 
 <body>According to most sitcoms that I watch... Yes. We are entering a world dominated by women. Or are as my nerdy half cousin would call it: "We are about to interface with the orifice of a matriarchtical society, flamen!"</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_3149_48124020"> 
<user id ="MS_143549239"> 
	 <username>[lifeizeazy]</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>20</age> 
	 <city>where ignorance surrounds me[charleston]</city> 
	 <province>South Carolina</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1219004040</date> 
 <body>all of this shit is funny.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_3149_48126149"> 
<user id ="MS_401743316"> 
	 <username>Jane</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>SAN LUIS OBISPO</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1219007760</date> 
 <body>Personally? I think everything is based on personal merit.  I've come up against several men of power in my life who are inherently sexist, but I have never failed to get what I wanted because I never let them regard me in a lower way. I think if you have enough respect for yourself and a general air of confidence, you can get most things done.  This is probably because I grew up training horses with guys though. You can whine, bitch, and moan.  I think women are definitely at a disadvantage because there is a high percentage who rely on being cute to get their way... which can work to an extent, but not in a way which will earn you any kind of respect in the future. More likely a pat on the head and a send her on her way.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_3149_48126408"> 
<user id ="MS_143549239"> 
	 <username>[lifeizeazy]</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>20</age> 
	 <city>where ignorance surrounds me[charleston]</city> 
	 <province>South Carolina</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1219008180</date> 
 <body> soooo how the hell does that put other women at a disadvantage?LOL..don't even answer.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_3149_48126485"> 
<user id ="MS_401743316"> 
	 <username>Jane</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>SAN LUIS OBISPO</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1219008300</date> 
 <body>   Haha, I will answer.  Because, if some chick screws her boss to get a raise, how much respect is there in that? She's basically a whore.  That's an extreme example, but generally the meaning is the same. I don't respect girls who use their looks to get what they want in the work place.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_3149_48126610"> 
<user id ="MS_143549239"> 
	 <username>[lifeizeazy]</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>20</age> 
	 <city>where ignorance surrounds me[charleston]</city> 
	 <province>South Carolina</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1219008540</date> 
 <body> Key Phrase:"She's basically a whore."  ...</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_3149_48126668"> 
<user id ="MS_401743316"> 
	 <username>Jane</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>SAN LUIS OBISPO</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1219008720</date> 
 <body>That's what I'm saying. There's no respect in that relationship. So how can they be equal?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_3149_48133767"> 
<user id ="MS_211791136"> 
	 <username>♥Cawaii♥</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>20</age> 
	 <city>Tampa</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1219028520</date> 
 <body>This thread just made my morning. :)</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>