<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_11095_50341780"> 
<user id ="MS_226698859"> 
	 <username>George Dunning</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>UK</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country></country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1222691820</date> 
 <body>  My thought is why did you have to say GTFO. Could you not simply talk to me instead of insult me?  Sheltered background? You really know nothing about me, do you?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11095_50370886"> 
<user id ="MS_7206379"> 
	 <username>Jock MacAbre</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>22</age> 
	 <city>St Helens,</city> 
	 <province>Northwest</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1222741980</date> 
 <body></body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11095_50378685"> 
<user id ="MS_406181688"> 
	 <username>Keith</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>27</age> 
	 <city>Massachusetts</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1222758240</date> 
 <body>I think someone should comment on my comment</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11095_50394592"> 
<user id ="MS_226698859"> 
	 <username>George Dunning</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>UK</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country></country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1222776480</date> 
 <body>  GTFO is still telling people where to go which is pretty disrespectful.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11095_50396291"> 
<user id ="MS_7206379"> 
	 <username>Jock MacAbre</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>22</age> 
	 <city>St Helens,</city> 
	 <province>Northwest</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1222778160</date> 
 <body>  Are you 12?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11095_50776307"> 
<user id ="MS_226698859"> 
	 <username>George Dunning</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>UK</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country></country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1223389680</date> 
 <body>To be honest, I can't be bothered having a row with someone I've never met.  If I think telling someone to GTFO is rude then it's hardly a surprise if I find it rude when someone says it to me. I don't care if you don't think it's rude.  I'm gonna leave it at that.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11095_50777344"> 
<user id ="MS_155282312"> 
	 <username>Swim fish! Swim!</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>36</age> 
	 <city>Glasgow</city> 
	 <province>Scotland</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1223391000</date> 
 <body>  A bit late in the day but you're right, you will get flayed for this.  This is the argument that Kelvin McKenzie tried to use when doing a bit of Jock bashing on quesiton time.  However, the true figures that came about later showed that out of the UK Scotland was the only part that received what it gave, ie we are self sufficient, if you include the revenues from Scottish gas and oil which at present has been subsidising the rest of the UK since the 70s.  Scotland says it pays its way and does not need English taxes · Analysis assigns all North Sea revenues to Edinburgh · Spendthrift claims based on 'myths and mistakes'  James Meikle The Guardian, Saturday November 3 2007 Article history Scotland pays its own way despite its depiction as a spendthrift nation abusing the generosity of English taxpayers, according to a new analysis of government spending. And far from receiving an unfair proportion of the tax pot, the breakdown shows that Scotland gets less public spending per head than Northern Ireland or London. Tax revenues from Scotland almost match the country's £49.2bn a year public spending - although only if all North Sea oil and gas revenues are attributed to Edinburgh, a controversial allocation.  The research, published yesterday by the Glasgow Herald, is based on Treasury figures in Whitehall, an analysis by consultants Oxford Economics and the newspaper's own calculations.  Tired of the clamour from English politicians and the London-based media for Gordon Brown to rein in the Scottish executive's spending, the paper said much of the "mischief" was based on a series of myths, mistakes and misconceptions.  David Cameron has signalled that he would review the Treasury system for sharing government funds across the country, adding that people should not think "there was some magic pot of gold" in England. Former Sun editor Kelvin Mackenzie also attacked "our tartan chums" for taking the "clever wealth-creators" of England for granted.  Critics say that Scots receive £1,500 a head more than people living in England, but the new analysis suggests the truth is more complicated. Despite its pockets of deprivation - one-third of the UK's landmass and far-flung communities are in Scotland - the average £9,631 public spending per head is less than London's £9,748 or Northern Ireland's £10,271. While cities such as Glasgow receive high levels of incapacity benefit, the overall welfare bill per head, £3,086, is lower in Scotland than in large parts of northern England.  The tax take from Scotland is only outranked by London, illustrating how Scots and their businesses are making their contribution to UK coffers, the report said. Not only did the North Sea bonanza swell Britain's public purse, but the nation's heavy smokers, though banned from smoking in public places before the rest of Britain, swelled the tobacco duty contributions disproportionately, contributing more than £1bn a year out of a UK £8bn.  Alex Salmond, Scotland's first minister, said: "This destroys the myth that Scotland is anything other than a resource-rich nation, well capable of flourishing with independence. Of course, the myth of the subsidised Scot has been peddled not just by Westminster Tories and the English tabloids , but also by politicians in Scotland for their own partisan ends."  The Herald's senior commentator, Alf Young, said the picture was far more nuanced than the black and white certainties of London-based tabloids. "Scotland is not some subsidy-obsessed outrider of the British state, offering little in return by way of tax revenues. There are other parts of the UK which receive higher per capita allocations of public expenditure."</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11095_50777554"> 
<user id ="MS_155282312"> 
	 <username>Swim fish! Swim!</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>36</age> 
	 <city>Glasgow</city> 
	 <province>Scotland</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1223391360</date> 
 <body>  I'll refer you to my explanation. taxation has been a bit murky in the UK with whitehall for decades fleecing Scotland whilst perpetrating the myth that Scotland scrounges off the rich south.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11095_50881157"> 
<user id ="MS_226698859"> 
	 <username>George Dunning</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>UK</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country></country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1223557860</date> 
 <body>Hi, Swim,fish,swim.  What are your thoughts on English students being forced into debt because your ministers voted that we should pay their students tuition fees?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11095_50932128"> 
<user id ="MS_249195709"> 
	 <username>Jock McCensored</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>22</age> 
	 <city>St Helens</city> 
	 <province>Northwest</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1223644980</date> 
 <body>  You say that, but did you leave it at that?  Nah, they whiney little bitch sent me a private message letting me know how much of a prat i was, and that my opinion means nothing to him(which is obviously true, because ofcourse, when youre so unaffected by someone, you have to send them angry message letting them know), and all that was before he mentioned that it would be extremely childish of me to reveal all this in the forums. Ooops!</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>