<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_10693_51100057"> 
<user id ="MS_3449431"> 
	 <username>Pre$ton</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>36</age> 
	 <city>Bel Air</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1223929740</date> 
 <body>It is also when the subprime mortgage frenzy was beginning to really boom.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10693_51105534"> 
<user id ="MS_3449431"> 
	 <username>Pre$ton</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>36</age> 
	 <city>Bel Air</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1223944680</date> 
 <body>I have been reading up on the Community Reinvestment Act, have any of you?  Opposite of subprime  CRA-motivated loans tend to be the opposite of subprime loans, most of which were issued by mortgage brokers and mortgage companies and financed by investment banks, none of which were covered by the CRA.  Here's more evidence that you've been hoodwinked. This information was collected by the Center for Responsible Lending:  • The CRA was effective long before the subprime market existed.  • The CRA has been around for three decades and the financial instruments that allowed the subprime mortgage industry to rise and crash came into existence within the past five years.  • Investment banks, not the federal government, had the appetite for risky loans.  The Wall Street-based market for reselling subprime created the demand for riskier loans. Because the debt would be sold into the market and not kept on the lender's books, many lenders did not bother to verify a borrower's income or assess ability to repay the loan.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10693_51122498"> 
<user id ="MS_292570269"> 
	 <username>RED NECK</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>99</age> 
	 <city>northwest</city> 
	 <province>Washington</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1223981520</date> 
 <body>hey freak you're talking to yourself  no one believes you cuz you lie too much oh wow yu read the cra woo i'm impressed your so smart...worship yourself</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10693_51122814"> 
<user id ="MS_392244934"> 
	 <username>Goat vs. Sheep vs. Sheeple</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>23</age> 
	 <city>OMAHA</city> 
	 <province>Nebraska</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1223981820</date> 
 <body> So prove his lies wrong.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10693_51123012"> 
<user id ="MS_399467372"> 
	 <username>JM</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>33</age> 
	 <city>Wisconsin</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1223982060</date> 
 <body>  I thought you were blaming Bush before.. What's going on with that?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10693_51123745"> 
<user id ="MS_3449431"> 
	 <username>Pre$ton</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>36</age> 
	 <city>Bel Air</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1223982840</date> 
 <body>  I'm building my case.  So far, you're not denying any of it. LOL</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10693_51129833"> 
<user id ="MS_2698434"> 
	 <username>Adam</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>26</age> 
	 <city>St. Louis</city> 
	 <province>Missouri</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1223989320</date> 
 <body>Right.  Say I'm a mortgage lender. Just because I make mortgages doesn't mean I keep them on my books. I make the mortgage and then sell that mortgage to Fannie Mae or Freddie Mac.  Both Fannie and Freddie were buying up a ton of private mortgages. Just because they did not create the initial mortgage doesn't mean that they did not eventually own the mortgage.  Mortgage lenders were being unscrupulous but when you know you can make a shitty mortgage, turn around and sell it to Fannie and Freddie, and still make a profit there is a definite moral hazard.  As I've said before Fannie Mae and Freddy Mac facilitated this problem.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10693_51129919"> 
<user id ="MS_3449431"> 
	 <username>Pre$ton</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>36</age> 
	 <city>Bel Air</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1223989440</date> 
 <body>Fannie and Freddie held a small percentage of these bad mortgages. You would know that if you read the info provided for you.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10693_51130243"> 
<user id ="MS_392244934"> 
	 <username>Goat vs. Sheep vs. Sheeple</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>23</age> 
	 <city>OMAHA</city> 
	 <province>Nebraska</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1223989800</date> 
 <body> Question:  Did you lend to people without down payments by issuing ARMS? Why did you do it? Did their income match up to what they could traditionally afford?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10693_51130256"> 
<user id ="MS_2698434"> 
	 <username>Adam</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>26</age> 
	 <city>St. Louis</city> 
	 <province>Missouri</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1223989800</date> 
 <body>Ok, I read the whole article. The most I saw was that as of 2006 Fannie and Freddie had gone from holding 56% to 24% of subprime loans. Thats a reduction yes, but in portfolio terms that is still a HUGE amount weighted toward a risky asset.  The bundled mortgage securities that fannie and freddie offer were seen as minimal risk investments and the fact that 24% of there holdings were in the subprime market sounds downright ludicrous to me.  However, maybe i missed something in the article saying that they only held a small percentage of these loans. can you point me to it?</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>