<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_27917_51147589"> 
<user id ="MS_335467485"> 
	 <username>trevor</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>SAFETY HARBOR</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1224012660</date> 
 <body>There has been talk now surrounding this game being turned into a motion picture. concidering this is actually a part of the Star Wars saga I wouldn't be surprised if this does become a movie one day down the line. what does everyone else think?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_27917_51159080"> 
<user id ="MS_2503485"> 
	 <username>Shawn</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>32</age> 
	 <city>Clearwater</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1224047880</date> 
 <body>   I hope not. It's a great game and all,but I'd rather see a movie based on something after ROTJ. Enough of the Clone Wars and anything between the existing movies. Give us something new for a change.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_27917_51160521"> 
<user id ="MS_22448491"> 
	 <username>Christophe O'Blivion™</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>29</age> 
	 <city>Hampshire</city> 
	 <province>London and South East</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1224050760</date> 
 <body>Oh God! No more fucking Star Wars, please..(!)</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_27917_51163371"> 
<user id ="MS_8135016"> 
	 <username>Jeffsta</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>22</age> 
	 <city>Fullerton</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1224055320</date> 
 <body>I think it'll never happen.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_27917_51163533"> 
<user id ="MS_19570081"> 
	 <username>Freak</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>California</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1224055620</date> 
 <body>  I know, seriously! And this is coming from a huge Star Wars fan too. I'm starting to get pretty sick of it.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_27917_51169754"> 
<user id ="MS_335467485"> 
	 <username>trevor</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>SAFETY HARBOR</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1224063720</date> 
 <body>  Well George Lucas swore that there would NEVER be an Epsiode 7,8 and 9 and concidering that Mark Hamill is old now just leaves out the possibility right there as well. Reason I think The Force Unleashed would work is because the story is right there. The story is actually in between the Episodes and is explained well on what happened to the Jedi and who finished them off.  I beaten the game and do believe that alot of the segments would work well in the movie. The part where the secret apprentice takes down a Star Destroyer with his force powers would deffinitally work well in the film as so would his fights against the Jedi he was tasked to kill. Also the ending sequence would most certainly make the film as well if it does happen.  I still have yet to see The Clone Wars movie and TV show and am awaiting the live action Bounty Hunter series due in 2011 but if there is any TRUE Star Wars film to be made it would have to be The Force Unleashed in my own opinion.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_27917_51176132"> 
<user id ="MS_118204420"> 
	 <username>Dain bramaged</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>29</age> 
	 <city>The last place you look</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1224070500</date> 
 <body> Star Wars should be left alone, unless it's Knights of the Old Republic and has nothing to do with Lucas. I'm sick of Lucas raping stormtroopers and spitting in the face of fans.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_27917_51177157"> 
<user id ="MS_335467485"> 
	 <username>trevor</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>SAFETY HARBOR</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1224071700</date> 
 <body>  I will admit I would love to see a KOTOR movie but it will not happen until George Lucas sells his rights. I will also go on to admit that Epsidoe 1 n 2 were not so impressive and thankfully Epsiode 3 was THE best in the prequels. The fact Episode 3 took a darker turn was THE best choice for the final installment. Also it isn't George Lycas' fault he cannot direct anymore. Before agreeing to Write/direct Episode 1,2 and 3, George Lucas hasn't directed since Episode 4 which was released in 1977.  After Epsidoe 4 he just produced the Indiana Jones Trilogy and along with Star Wars Episode 5 and 6. It was a shame that Episode 1 n 2 weren't that good but at least they were decent. I still have yet to see The Clone Wars show so there is no telling if George Lucas gotten worse or a tad bit better.  Anyhow I personally think a Force Unleashed film would work if handled right</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_27917_51179467"> 
<user id ="MS_118204420"> 
	 <username>Dain bramaged</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>29</age> 
	 <city>The last place you look</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1224074280</date> 
 <body> The prequels being 3 of the worst movies is hardly a secret.The only redeeming quality of the three were Qui-Gon Jinn and Darth Maul, and in typical Lucas fashion he took the only good things in the films and killed them. Hayden Christensen's acting is on par with Keanu Reeves, but considering the ep 1-3 held little continuity to the original 3, I guess his horrible acting falls short of being the top reason things went wrong.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_27917_51194950"> 
<user id ="MS_335467485"> 
	 <username>trevor</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>SAFETY HARBOR</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1224093300</date> 
 <body>  Hayden Christensen was likely THE worst cast for Anakin Sykwalker. I figured either George Lucas either wanted a bargain bin actor or he just couldn't find anyone else to replace him. I remembered after Episode 2 came into theaters it was rumored that Hugh Jackman was to take over the role of Anakin Sykwalker. Reason that was the rumor was because it was said at the time that Episode 3 would take place a big amount of years after Episode 2.  It was right when Episode 3 went into production that everyone around saw that the rumor was false and Hayden was back.I personally liked Episode 3 alot and did appreciate alot of the things in it. I liked the entire beginning with the battle over Coruscant took place which lead to the duel between Anakin and Count Dooku.  I also liked how the emperor held a lightsaber and did combat with Yoda and also the whole battle sequence between General Grievous and Obi Wan was surely entertaining. I liked Episode 3 and it would be entertaining to see The Force Unleashed turned into a film. if it is written well and has a good director on board I would be satisfied.  If The Force Unleashed is turned into a film I would highly doubt George Lucas would direct. He would most likely co write and probably produce. The least Star Wars brand he would direct would be some of the episodes on the upcoming live action TV show due in late 2011.</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>