<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_8694_51800115"> 
<user id ="MS_22447875"> 
	 <username>Visionary1</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>47</age> 
	 <city>de' troit</city> 
	 <province>Michigan</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225175580</date> 
 <body>Palin drags down Republican ticket By DAVID LIGHTMAN SarahPalin has become a drag on the Republican presidential ticket, thefirst time in recent political history that a running mate has madesuch a difference. Among many independents and moderate Republicans,she's raised serious questions about John McCain's judgment, become toomuch of a national punch line and reinforced concerns about McCain'sage. "Nice lady, no experience. It's so sad. She's a giganticdrag," said Chris DePino, a Republican consultant based in New Haven,Conn. The Alaska governor does help the ticket somewhat byenergizing hard-core Republicans, but polls suggest that overall "she'shurting John McCain," said Andrew Kohut, the president of the PewResearch Center. In a nationwide survey Oct. 16-19, Pew foundthat 49 percent of respondents had unfavorable views of Palin, while 44percent saw her favorably. A month earlier, 54 percent had seen herfavorably and 32 percent viewed her negatively. Typically,post-election polls find that vice-presidential choices sway about 1percent of voters. This time, Kohut said, "we'll get a much biggernumber." A key reason is that "the Palin choice reflects poorlyon Senator McCain's judgment," said vice presidential expert JoelGoldstein, a professor of law at St. Louis University. Pew foundthat 41 percent of respondents thought McCain showed "poor judgment"overall, while 29 percent said that of Democratic nominee Barack Obama.While McCain's number isn't solely because of his choice of Palin, herselection was a factor. McCain's age is also a reason for voters'concern about Palin. The Arizona senator is 72 and has had fourinstances of melanoma, the most serious type of skin cancer. MayoClinic physicians have posted a detailed explanation of McCain'scondition and treatment on his Web site. The prognosis, they said, was"good." Worries linger, however. "If something happened toMcCain, she would not be qualified to step in and be president," saidAnnette Barron, an independent voter from Altamonte Springs, Fla. Palinalso has hurt herself by becoming largely invisible to the generalpublic, except when she got media attention for starting controversies- such as charging that Obama was "palling around with terrorists" - orfor receiving $150,000 in clothing and accessories from the RepublicanParty. She also unabashedly identifies herself with the party's conservative wing, alienating moderates. "Itreinforced the notion that John McCain cared little about people likeme," said former Maine state Rep. Sherry Huber, a Republican who backedMcCain in the primary but now supports Obama. "She clearly does notshare the values I and other moderate Republicans do." ProminentRepublicans have echoed that idea. Sen. Lindsey Graham, R-S.C., one ofMcCain's closest friends, suggested that Sen. Joseph Lieberman, anindependent Democrat from Connecticut, would have brought independentsto the ticket. Last week, former Pennsylvania Gov. Tom Ridge said thathad McCain picked him, the Republican Party would have had a bettershot at winning his state. Then there's Palin's image problembecause of what vice-presidential expert Timothy Walch called "thealbatross of American comedy." "Every time (comedian) Tina Feyappeared on TV imitating her, it diminished Palin," said Walch, thedirector of the Herbert Hoover presidential library. "For somebodyessentially unknown, she's diminished when she becomes a caricature ofherself." In most election years, Palin would have been afootnote, like controversial vice-presidential choices Spiro Agnew in1968 or Dan Quayle 20 years later. Both were lightly regarded buttriumphed on winning tickets. However, Goldstein, of St. LouisUniversity, noted that in 1968, Richard Nixon was 55, so the prospectof an Agnew presidency seemed dim. In 1988, Quayle ran with George H.W.Bush, who was essentially running for President Reagan's third termagainst unpopular Democrat Michael Dukakis. In 2008, Goldsteinsaid, Obama "has convinced a broad cross-section of the American peoplehe's presidential," so Palin gives swing voters who are warming to theIllinois senator one more reason to move away from McCain. As forPalin's expected appeal to women, Sieglinde Warren, a teachingsupervisor from Poland, Ohio, was a Clinton supporter who now backsObama. Palin and Clinton don't compare, she said, because "Clinton hadsome substance I could relate to." (EDITORS: END OPTIONAL TRIM) Tobe sure, Palin has had some positive impact on the campaign. McCain hadnever been a favorite of strict conservatives, as he challengedRepublican orthodoxy over the years on tax cuts, campaign finance,climate change and other topics. The Republican base loves Palin. "Somany people can relate to her. She really appeals to everydayhousewives, people who go out and hunt, and people who have done greatthings in their life," said Bob Dodge, a retired communicationsengineer in Sarasota, Fla. And don't tell Jennifer Tarman, aBradenton, Fla., medical assistant, that Palin, who's been a governorsince December 2006, isn't qualified. "She's more qualified thanObama," she said. Obama's been a U.S. senator since January 2005, buthas spent most of the past two years campaigning for the White House. Still, the experts and a lot of swing voters agree with Goldstein. "She's made it much more difficult for McCain," he said. ON THE WEB John McCain's medical records: http://www.johnmccain.com/mccainrecords/</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8694_51800147"> 
<user id ="MS_23377261"> 
	 <username>THERIOT</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>Lafayette</city> 
	 <province>Louisiana</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225175640</date> 
 <body>Ha yea her speeches are written yet three McCain political consultants went on national television complaining that Palin was not giving the responses written for her..damn her for having a mind of her own..do you really believe that people who take chances and make something of themselves should give half of their earnings to the people who take advantage of the government handouts..please explain how that makes any sense..my father is a small business owner.. He worked for 15 years as a draftsman and project manager making just enough to support his three children and wife..He took advantage of the fact that he lives in the greatest country in the world and started his own business..it was only by the grace of god and a few good friends that he made it through the first years of business..His contracting business is now a corporation and he does make over 250k a year..he lives in a three bedroom 1k sq.foot home with his wife and I. pretty average..yet he pays %40 of what he makes in one year to the government to support the nigger sitting on the street with her three children on welfare..yea i guess you think thats "american"</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8694_51800177"> 
<user id ="MS_191634299"> 
	 <username>Skull</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>100</age> 
	 <city>Illinois</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225175700</date> 
 <body>I think the news media is pushing Obama because they remember how many news papers sold during the Clinton Years...</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8694_51800232"> 
<user id ="MS_23377261"> 
	 <username>THERIOT</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>Lafayette</city> 
	 <province>Louisiana</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225175820</date> 
 <body>oh yea..please list Obama's accomplishments and level of experience..then research Palin and do the same..Its prettyt sad to think our candidate for vice president has more experience than your presidential candidate..</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8694_51800387"> 
<user id ="MS_220823514"> 
	 <username>Momma Bear</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>38</age> 
	 <city>Hughesville</city> 
	 <province>Pennsylvania</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225176120</date> 
 <body> Well at least you tried; it is sad that individuals post about someone’s experience and forget the candidate they are voting for has less.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8694_51800572"> 
<user id ="MS_57775192"> 
	 <username>Phillip</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>22</age> 
	 <city>HARRISON</city> 
	 <province>TENNESSEE</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225176480</date> 
 <body>    Really?   Obama: Running local community projects.  12 years of State/National political experience.    Palin: 10 years city experience. 2 years state experience.     I guess if running a small city is now more important than passing state legislation...</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8694_51800761"> 
<user id ="MS_12550638"> 
	 <username>pete</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>56</age> 
	 <city>ontario</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>CA</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225176780</date> 
 <body>Sarah Palin is INCOMPETENT and Unqualified!   Ohh no, what gave her away, yes but McCain says her hubby Todd is a strong and will make a good second man because he raced his snowmobile with a broken arm..  Ohh mannn lmao</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8694_51800788"> 
<user id ="MS_297990128"> 
	 <username>David Ortez</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>24</age> 
	 <city>Houston</city> 
	 <province>Texas</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225176840</date> 
 <body>Please use the little intelligence you do have and read up about your candidate. Even her own advisers dissent about her qualifications.  A Palin associate and McCain adviser, according to CNN, defended their strategy of limiting Palin’s interaction with the media because “she was not ready and that the missteps could have been a lot worse.”  "Her lack of fundamental understanding of some key issues was dramatic," said another McCain source with direct knowledge of the process to prepare Palin after she was picked. The source said it was probably the "hardest" to get her "up to speed than any candidate in history."  Read more about it @ http://www.cnn.com/2008/POLITICS/10/27/palin.tension/index.html</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8694_51800837"> 
<user id ="MS_883588"> 
	 <username>stephinitely, maybe.</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>22</age> 
	 <city>321</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225176960</date> 
 <body>   executive experience > nonexecutive experience.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8694_51800858"> 
<user id ="MS_727366"> 
	 <username>Paul</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>28</age> 
	 <city>UpperEastSide</city> 
	 <province>New York</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225176960</date> 
 <body>  A small city that doesn't have jurisdiction over the schools, fire department, social services...  The mayor of Wasilla is responsible for less than an Applebees Manager.</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>