<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_8694_51800761"> 
<user id ="MS_12550638"> 
	 <username>pete</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>56</age> 
	 <city>ontario</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>CA</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225176780</date> 
 <body>Sarah Palin is INCOMPETENT and Unqualified!   Ohh no, what gave her away, yes but McCain says her hubby Todd is a strong and will make a good second man because he raced his snowmobile with a broken arm..  Ohh mannn lmao</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8694_51800788"> 
<user id ="MS_297990128"> 
	 <username>David Ortez</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>24</age> 
	 <city>Houston</city> 
	 <province>Texas</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225176840</date> 
 <body>Please use the little intelligence you do have and read up about your candidate. Even her own advisers dissent about her qualifications.  A Palin associate and McCain adviser, according to CNN, defended their strategy of limiting Palin’s interaction with the media because “she was not ready and that the missteps could have been a lot worse.”  "Her lack of fundamental understanding of some key issues was dramatic," said another McCain source with direct knowledge of the process to prepare Palin after she was picked. The source said it was probably the "hardest" to get her "up to speed than any candidate in history."  Read more about it @ http://www.cnn.com/2008/POLITICS/10/27/palin.tension/index.html</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8694_51800837"> 
<user id ="MS_883588"> 
	 <username>stephinitely, maybe.</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>22</age> 
	 <city>321</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225176960</date> 
 <body>   executive experience > nonexecutive experience.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8694_51800858"> 
<user id ="MS_727366"> 
	 <username>Paul</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>28</age> 
	 <city>UpperEastSide</city> 
	 <province>New York</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225176960</date> 
 <body>  A small city that doesn't have jurisdiction over the schools, fire department, social services...  The mayor of Wasilla is responsible for less than an Applebees Manager.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8694_51800887"> 
<user id ="MS_57775192"> 
	 <username>Phillip</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>22</age> 
	 <city>HARRISON</city> 
	 <province>TENNESSEE</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225177020</date> 
 <body>    Last I checked, the Vice President, as a position, has no direct executive responsibilities. In fact, it is more of a legislative job. Maybe she is running for the wrong position?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8694_51800904"> 
<user id ="MS_101724615"> 
	 <username>*(ch EE ts)*</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>20</age> 
	 <city>SO CAL BITCH!</city> 
	 <province>CALIFORNIA</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225177020</date> 
 <body> Really? So someone didn't come up with Joe six-pack or Catie Citizen or Tito the Builder or any of those other cute nicknames she uses to describe the US masses? Those stereotypes are all hers? What about the constant lectures about Obama and Biden instead of Answering the questions about her foreign and economic policies? Really? That was all her huh, well, now my confidence in her is even lower.... Thanks!</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8694_51800905"> 
<user id ="MS_23377261"> 
	 <username>THERIOT</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>Lafayette</city> 
	 <province>Louisiana</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225177020</date> 
 <body>ever heard of socialism?? racism?? yes black people can be racist too..</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8694_51800908"> 
<user id ="MS_12550638"> 
	 <username>pete</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>56</age> 
	 <city>ontario</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>CA</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225177080</date> 
 <body>   Haahahahhahahahah now that was funnyy lmao</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8694_51802048"> 
<user id ="MS_297990128"> 
	 <username>David Ortez</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>24</age> 
	 <city>Houston</city> 
	 <province>Texas</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225179000</date> 
 <body>Sarah Palin has more executive experience than Barack Obama ... Joe Biden and guess who? John McCain.  Please stop using that talking point as if it were valid. Using that same argument your unqualified VP has more experience than John McCain who has never managed anything.  George W. Bush has more Executive experience than John McCain in 2000 and we all know how that turned out.  She was managed a state of 600k people, not even 1 million. According to those standards ... Mayors, not Governors, have managed a staff and population greater than Alaska. Barack Obama, as a senator, has more constituents in his district than Palin in her state.  Do you see how flawed your argument becomes?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_8694_51802237"> 
<user id ="MS_30453418"> 
	 <username>Hippie Dyke Voted for Obama</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>ROSEVILLE</city> 
	 <province>Michigan</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1225179300</date> 
 <body>  OWNED!! You rock!  *applause*</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>